Maintaining FL310.
保持飞行高度层 310。
Descending to FL290.
下降到飞行高度层 290。
Reaching FL190.
到达高度层 190。
Maintaining FL90 over WXJ.
过 WXJ 时保持高度层 90。
Continue descent to 3000 feet， QNH 1012.
继续下降到 3000 英尺，修正海压 1012。
Passing FL180 for FL310.
通过高度层 180，继续上升到高度层 310。
Cleared to enter controlled airspace not above FL100.
可以进入管制空域，不高于高度层 100。
Request further climb.
请示进一步爬升。
Fly direct to SHA, not below FL180.
直飞 SHA，高度不低于高度层 180。
After passing CGO descend to FL80.
过 CGO 后，下降到高度层 80。
Stop descent at FL210.
到高度层 210 时停止下降。
Descending to reach FL150 by WXI.
到 WXI 前下降到高度层 150。
Unable to reach FL150 by ZHO due performance.
性能原因到 ZHO 之前不能到达高度层 150。
Climbing to FL290, to be level by 55.
爬升到高度层 290，55 分前改平。
Descend at 2000 feet per minute.
以 2000 英尺每分下降率下降。
Climbing at 1000 feet per minute or greater.
以每分 1000 英尺或更大的爬升率上升。
When ready, descend to FL210, level at PLT.
准备好时下降到高度层 210，在 PLT 改平。
Right heading 330, descending to 3000 feet, cleared for ILS approach Runway 36R.
右转航向 330，下降到 3000 英尺，可以盲降进近，跑道 36 右。
Descend to 3000 feet, information P is current.
下降到 3000 英尺，最新通播 Papa。
Expedite descent to FL180.
加速下降到高度层 180。
Expedite climb to FL190.
加速上升到高度层 190。
Climb to FL280 expedite until passing FL180.
上升到高度层 280，快速爬升直到通过高度层 180。
Unable to expedite climb due weight.
重量原因不能加速爬升。
Descending immediately to FL200 due traffic.
由于冲突飞机，立即下降到高度层 200。
When ready, climb to FL280, report leaving FL200.
准备好时上升高度层 280，离开高度层 200 时报。
Leaving FL200, climbing to FL280.
离开高度层 200，爬升到高度层 280。
Maintaining own separation and VMC, descending to FL80.
自己保持间隔和目视气象条件，下降到高度层 80。
Reaching 8000 feet, request further climb.
到达 8000 英尺，请示进一步上升。
Cancel SID, track direct to LLK, climb to and maintain FL110.
取消 SID（标准仪表离场程序），直飞 LLK，上升并保持高度层 110。
Experiencing icing condition. Request further descent.
遇到结冰条件，请示进一步下降。
Icing condition encountered. Request further climb.
遇到结冰条件，请示进一步爬升。
Experiencing severe turbulence. Request further descent.
遭遇严重颠簸，请示进一步下降。
Reduce speed to Mach decimal 76.
减速到马赫数点 76。
Maintain Mach point 84 or greater.
保持马赫数不小于点 84。
Maintain Mach point 80 or less.
保持马赫数不大于点 80。
Maintain present speed.
保持当前速度。
Maintain 250 knots or greater.
保持速度不小于 250 节。
Reduce to minimum clean speed.
减速到最小光洁速度。
Reduce to minimum approach speed.
减速到最小进近速度。
Maintain 160 knots until 4 miles final.
保持速度 160 节直到五边 4 海里。
Maintain 160 knots until outer marker.
保持速度 160 节直到外指点标。
Descend to FL120, on speed conversion, 250 knots.
下降到高度层 120，调速到 250 节。
Cancel speed restriction, continue descent to 7000 feet.
取消速度限制，继续下降到 7000 英尺。
LMN-02 Departure, passing 2500 feet climbing to 9000 feet.
LMN-02 离场，通过 2500 英尺，继续上升到 9000 英尺。
Maintaining FL350, cleared to destination, flight planned route.
保持高度层 350，可以按计划航路飞往目的地机场，
Request radar vectors for visual approach Runway 22.
请示雷达引导，目视进近，跑道 22。
Request join downwind Runway 31.
请示加入 31 跑道三边。
Request taxi to holding point Runway 13.
请示滑行到 13 跑道等待点。
Request taxi to south maintenance ramp.
请示滑行到南维修机坪。
Request frequency change.
请示切换频率。
15NM to HRB, FL290, tracking to JMU, squawking 6543.
据 HRB 15 海里，高度层 290，直飞 JMU，应答机 6543。
Contact Control on 118.9.
联系区调 118.9。
Position OBLIK at 0646, maintaining FL310, estimating ZF 0658, WUH next.
当前位置 OBLIK，时间 0646，高度层 310 保持，预计 ZF 点时间 0658，下一位置 WUH。
Next report at WXA.
下一报告点 WXA。
Omit position reports.
省略位置报。
Omit position reports on this frequency.
本频率省略位置报。
Resume position reporting.
恢复位置报。
Delay not determined due runway obstruction.
由于跑道障碍物，延误待定。
Approach time not determined due weather.
由于天气，进近时间待定。
Slot time not determined due flow control.
流控，离场时间待定。
Revised slot time at 56.
修改的离场时间为 56 分。
Expect hold at HUR VOR for 10 minutes due traffic.
由于冲突飞机，预计在 HUR VOR 等待 10 分钟。
Expected approach time 44.
预计进近时间 44 分。
Revised expected approach time 54.
最新预计的进近时间为 54 分。
No delay expected.
预计无延误。
Delay not determined, numerous aircraft holding for weather improvement.
延误不确定，很多飞机在等待天气好转。
Cleared to exit the hold, fly direct to ML. Contact Approach on 128.35.
可以推出等待，直飞 ML。联系进近 128.35。
Approach clearance canceled, turn left direct to DA, climb to 4000 feet, hold as published,expect further clearance at time 50.
取消进近许可，左转直飞 DA，上升到 4000 英尺，按公布的航图等待，预计进一步许可时间 50 分。
Ready for approach.
准备好进近了。
Request leave the holding pattern.
请示退出等待程序。
After passing SY VOR, leave the hold on heading 250, cleared for VOR approach Runway 06.
过 SY VOR 台后，推出等待，航向 250，可以 VOR 进近，跑道 06。
Leave JFK VOR heading 210.
离开 JFK VOR，航向 210。
Cleared to LHR, hold at LHR as published. Maintain 8000 feet. Expect further clearance at 18.
可以飞往 LHR，按公布的航图在 LHR 等待。保持高度 8000 英尺。预计进一步许可在 18分。
Hold south of AMS VOR at 9000 feet, inbound track 270 degrees, left hand pattern, outboundtime 1 minute. Expect further clearance at 46.
在 AMS VOR 台以南等待，高度 9000 英尺，向台航迹 270，左等待，出航时间 1 分钟。预计进一步许可时间 46 分。
Cleared to the 180 radial of PER VOR at 15 DME. Hold south, left hand pattern, outboundtime 2 minutes, expect approach clearance at 37.
可以在 PER VOR 台 180 度径向线 DME 15 海里处向南左等待，出航时间 2 分钟，预计进近许可时间 37 分。
Information P received, stand 03, ready to copy ATC clearance.
通播 P 收到，03 停机位准备好抄收 ATC 许可。
Gate 26, request clearance to London with information F.
26 停机位，请示去往伦敦的放行许可，通播 F 收到。
Cleared to destination, flight planned route, cruising level 330, departure Runway 04, initialaltitude 7000 feet. HZ-01 Departure, squawk 2563, departure frequency 124.35.
可以按计划放行到目的地，巡航高度层 330，离场跑道 04，起始高度 7000 英尺。HZ-01 离场，应答机 2563，离场频率 124.35。
Cleared to destination via ZAM, flight planned route, D03 Departure, cruising level 230,squawk 3763.
可以按计划航路经 ZAM 放行到目的地，D-03 离场，巡航高度层 230，应答机 3763。
Cleared to destination via flight planned route, Runway 36R, LKO-01 Departure, initially climbto 4500 feet, cruising level 310, when airborne contact 119.7, squawk 2515.
可以经计划航路放行到目的地，跑道 36 右，LKO-01 离场，起始爬升到 4500 英尺，巡航高度层 310，离地后联系 119.7，应答机 2515。
Cleared via ZF-01 Departure, initial altitude 5000 feet. Departure frequency 125.9. Cruisinglevel 290, departure Runway 04. Squawk 6563.
可以经 ZF-01 离场，起始高度 5000 英尺，离场频率 125.9，巡航高度层 290，离场跑道04，应答机 6563。
Cleared to destination via flight plan route. Departure Runway 36L. HZ-01D Departure. Initialaltitude 5000 feet. Cruising level 330. Departure frequency 119.45, squawk 5667.
可以按计划航路放行到目的地机场，离场跑道 36 左，HZ-01D 离场，起始高度 5000 英尺，巡航高度层 330。离场频率 119.45，应答机 5667。
Recleared to destination via ZF-01 Departure, Runway 36R, rest of clearance unchanged.
重新允许经 ZF-01 离场到目的地，跑道 36 右，其余航路不变。
Recleared to destination via B213, WHA, R343, rest of route unchanged.
重新允许经 B213，WHA、R343 飞往目的地，其余航路不变。
Cleared to destination via flight planned route, initial climb to 2700 feet, request level change en-route, departure frequency 120.3, squawk 0722.
可以按计划航路飞往目的地，起始上升到 2700 英尺，航路上申请改变高度，离场频率120.3，应答机 0722。
Gate15, information C, ready to copy ATC clearance.
15 停机位，通播 C 收到，准备好抄收 ATC 放行许可。
Cleared to destination, BK02 RNAV Departure, initially 3000 feet, departure frequency 125.4, squawk 3311.
可以飞往目的地机场，BK-02 RNAV 离场，起始高度 3000 英尺，离场频率 125.4，应答机3311。
Say again all after 3000 feet.
3000 英尺之后的内容再说一遍。
Say again all before departure frequency.
离场频率之前的内容再说一遍。
Say again the initial altitude.
再说一遍起始高度。
Unable to cross LX FL150 due weight, maintaining FL130.
重量原因，不能在高度层 150 通过 LX，保持高度层 130。
Destination Beijing, request departure information.
目的地北京，请示离场信息。
Bay24, request start-up.
24 号停机位，请示开车。
Start up approved, QNH 29.91.
可以开车，修正海压 29.91。
Start up approved, altimeter setting 29.91.
可以开车，高度表设置 29.91。
Start up at 35, QNH 997.
35 分开车，修正海压 997。
Expect start up at 35, QNH 1030.
预计 35 分开车，修正海压 1030。
Expect departure at 49, start up at own discretion, QNH 1004.
预计 49 分离场，开车时间自己掌握，修正海压 1004。
Radio check on 118.3.
118.3 校波。
I read you 5.
我听你 5 个。
You are unreadable.
无法听清。
Can you speak slower?
你能说慢点吗？
How do you read?
你听我声音怎样？
QNH 997, I say again, QNH 997.
修正海压 997，我再说一遍，修正海压 997。
Stand 27, request pushback.
停机位 27，请示推出。
Pushback approved, Runway 31.
可以推出，跑道 31。
Stand by pushback.
推出稍等。
Pushback at own discretion.
推出时间自己掌握。
Pushback approved, long pushback.
可以推出，多推点。
Pushback to taxiway A approved.
可以推出到滑行道 A。
Pushback approved, facing west.
可以推出，朝西。
Cancel pushback, we have maintenance problem.
取消推出，我们出现问题需要维修。
Ground, Cockpit. Ready for pushback.
地面，驾驶舱，推出准备好了。
Brakes released.
刹车释放了。
Starting Number One.
启动一发。
Brakes set, disconnect.
刹车刹住，断开。
Request taxi.
请示滑出。
Taxi via taxiway C to holding point Runway 24.
经由滑行道 C 滑至跑道 24 等待点。
Taxi to holding point Runway 24, traffic in sight.
划到跑道 24 等待点，看见飞机了。
Request taxi back for maintenance purpose.
请示滑回维修。
Negative. We need 10 minutes to cool the brakes.
不行，我们需要 10 分钟冷却刹车。
Approaching holding point, request crossing Runway 24.
接近等待点，请示穿过 24 跑道。
Hold short of Runway 24.
24 跑道外等待。
Holding, traffic in sight.
等待，飞机能见。
Cross Runway 24, report runway vacated.
穿过 24 跑道，脱离跑道报。
Unable to vacate via A2, request full length of runway.
不能经由滑行道 A2 脱离，请示全跑道。
Crossing Runway 24, wilco.
穿越跑道 24，照办。
Runway vacated.
脱离跑道。
Giving way to B747 passing from left to right.
给从左向右通过的波音 747 让道。
Follow the greens to holding point Runway 05R.
沿绿灯滑到跑道 05 右等待点。
Cross red stop-bar at A1, we understand stop-bar unserviceable.
A1 穿过红色停止灯，明白原来它不工作了。
After landing Airbus320, cross Runway 24, report vacated.
空客 320 落地后穿越跑道 24，脱离报。
Taxi to holding point C3, Runway 36.
滑到跑道 36 C3 等待点。
Behind Boeing747 passing left to right, taxi to holding point A1 Runway 24.
从左向右通过的波音 747 之后，滑到 24 跑道 A1 等待点。
Ready for departure.
离场准备好。
After departure, climb straight ahead until 3000 feet.
起飞后，直线爬升至 3000 英尺。
Cancel SID, maintain runway heading.
取消 SID，保持跑道航向。
Lining up Runway 01C.
对正 01C 跑道。
Ready for immediate departure.
立即起飞准备好。
Cleared for immediate takeoff.
可以立即起飞。
Runway 06, cleared for takeoff. Report airborne.
跑道 06，可以起飞，离地报。
Cleared for takeoff, Runway 06, wilco.
可以起飞，跑道 06，照办。
Airborne, passing 500 feet for 4000 feet.
离地，通过 500 英尺，继续上升 4000 英尺。
The airbus on final in sight.
看见了五边空客飞机。
Behind Airbus on short final, line up behind.
短五边空客飞机之后，对正跑道。
After departure, turn left heading 190, Runway 24R, cleared for takeoff.
起飞后，左转航向 190，跑道 24 右，可以起飞。
Request right turn when airborne due weather.
天气原因，请示离地后右转。
Take off immediately or hold short of runway.
立即起飞，否则跑道外等待。
Take off immediately or vacate runway.
立即起飞，否则脱离跑道。
Hold position, cancel takeoff, I say again, cancel takeoff.
原地等待，取消起飞，再说一遍，取消起飞。
Holding position.
原地等待。
Stopping! Engine fire.
中断起飞，发动机起火了。
Request return to ramp.
请示滑回机坪。
Tire burst, possible evacuation on runway.
爆胎了，可能要在跑道上疏散。
Negative intersection departure due performance.
由于性能限制，不能使用减跑道起飞。
Affirm. We can accept intersection departure from C2.
可以。我们接受从 C2 进跑道起飞。
Request intersection departure from C2.
请示从 C2 减跑道起飞。
Request Takeoff Runway Available (TORA) from intersection C2.
请问从 C2 起飞的可用跑道长度是多少？
Request Accelerate-Stop Distance Available (ASDA) from intersection D1.
请问从 D1 进跑道的可用加速停止距离是多少？
Request Takeoff Distance Available (TODA) from intersection E3.
请问 E3 道口的可用起飞距离是多少？
Line up and wait. Understand one aircraft to depart from A2.
对正跑道、等待。明白有飞机从 A2 起飞。
Taxi via A2, backtrack and line-up Runway 18.
经 A2 滑行，180 度调头，对正跑道 18。
Airbus 330 heavy, 8000 feet, Information X.
空客 330 重型，8000 英尺，通播 X 收到。
Join right-hand downwind, Runway 34.
加入 34 跑道右三边。
Number Two, follow airbus 330 on base.
第二个，跟着四边空客 330。
Number Two, traffic in sight.
第二个，看到了飞机。
Straight-in visual approach, Runway 34.
直接目视进近，跑道 34。
Extend downwind, Number Two, airbus 320 in sight.
延长三边，第二个落地，看见空客 320 了。
Orbit right. Number Two.
右转一圈，第二个。
Number Two, follow airbus 320 ahead.
第二个，跟着前机空客 320。
Make a short approach.
短五边进近。
Long final, airfield in sight.
长五边，机场可见。
Continue approach Runway 25.
继续进近，跑道 25。
Runway 27, cleared to land.
跑道 27，可以落地。
Short final, request wind check.
短五边，请问风向风速。
Request low pass due unsafe landing gear indication.
不安全起落架指示，请示低空通场。
Low pass approved Runway 27, not below 500 feet.
可以低空通场，跑道 27，高度不低于 500 英尺。
Landing clearance canceled. Continue approach.
取消落地许可。继续进近。
Behind the Boeing737, cleared to land.
跟着波音 737，可以落地。
Request low approach.
请示低高度进近。
Runway not in sight, going around.
跑道不可见，复飞了。
No contact at minimum, going around.
决断高，跑道不可见，复飞了。
Wind shear, going around.
风切变，复飞了。
Going around, localizer fluctuation.
复飞了，航向道波动。
Follow the standard missed approach procedure, climbing to 3000 feet.
按标准复飞程序，爬升到 3000 英尺。
Take first right. When vacated, contact Ground 118.35.
第一个道口右转。脱离跑道后，联系地面 118.35。
After vacated contact Ground 121.6.
脱离后联系地面 121.6。
Taxi to Stand 27 via Taxiway A.
经滑行道 A，滑行到停机位 27。
Taxi to the end of Runway.
滑到跑道末端。
Confirm construction work adjacent to Gate 37.
证实停机位 37 附近正在施工。
Confirm centerline taxiway lighting unserviceable.
证实中线滑行道灯不工作。
Confirm PAPI light unserviceable.
证实 PAPI 等不工作。
The Runway light is too bright. Request dim it.
跑道灯太亮，请调暗一些。
Flock of birds 3 miles final.
五边 3 海里处有鸟群活动。
Runway covered with patches of water, braking action medium.
大片水覆盖跑道，刹车效应中等。
Confirm airport rescue and fire facilities category.
证实机场救援和防火设备的种类。
Is the weather improving or deteriorating?
天气在转好，还是恶化？
Thicker patches of fog exist further along the runway. RVR significantly reduced.
跑道末端有浓雾，跑道视程明显变差。
Confirm current RVR less than 400 meters.
证实当前跑道视程小于 400 米。
Confirm visibility more than 1000 meters.
证实能见度大于 1000 米。
Is mid-point RVR available?
中点跑道视程可用吗？
Confirm RVR Runway 27.
证实跑道 27 的跑道视程。
RVR Runway 27 is 600 meters.
跑道 27 的跑道视程为 600 米。
Confirm touchdown RVR greater than 350 meters.
证实接地点跑道视程大于 350 米。
Confirm stop-end RVR 150 meters.
证实停止端跑道视程为 150 米。
Confirm midpoint RVR more than 550 meters.
证实中间跑道视程大于 550 米。
Confirm threshold Runway 27 displaced.
证实跑道 27 入口内移。
The runway surface is damp. Braking action good.
跑道道面潮湿，刹车效应好。
Confirm the reason for our flight suspension.
证实一下航班暂停的原因。
Confirm our flight has been suspended due bio-hazards at destination.
证实一下航班暂停是因为目的地机场生化物品泄露。
Confirm the reason for impounding our aircraft.
证实扣押我们飞机的原因。
Tow approved via A to remote apron.
可以经滑行道 A 拖至远机坪。
Request de-icing.
请示除冰。
Request frost removal only at the gate.
请示只在停机位除霜。
De-icing completed. Request taxi.
完成除冰，请示滑出。
Request start engine at the gate.
请示停机位开车。
Request time check.
请示校时。
Request backtrack.
请示掉头。
Unable BK-1A Departure due performance. Request BK-1B.
性能原因，不能 BK-1A 离场，请示 BK-1B 离场。
Request departure instruction.
请示离场指令。
When airborne, track extended center-line, cleared for takeoff, Runway 18.
离地后，保持跑道中心延长线方向，可以起飞，跑道 18。
Contact Arrival 118.050.
联系进近 118.050。
Request remote apron for maintenance purpose.
维修原因，请示远机坪停机。
Continue present heading.
继续当前航向。
Resume own navigation to BK.
恢复自主导航至 BK。
Confirm identification lost.
证实识别丢失。
Identified, position 50 miles east of BK.
已识别，位置 BK 以东 50 海里。
30 miles from touchdown, contact Approach 118.1.
离接地点 30 海里，联系进近 118.1。
Three sixty turn left.
左转 360 度。
Orbit left for delay.
延误，左转一圈。
Looking out.
正在寻找。
Traffic in sight.
看见飞机了。
Negative contact due IMC.
由于仪表气象条件，不能看见。
Traffic passed and clear.
冲突飞机已通过，无影响。
Squawk 7563.
应答机 7563.
Reset squawk 5101.
重置应答机 5101。
Squawk ident.
应答机识别。
Squawk standby.
应答机待命（模式）。
Squawk Charlie and code 5120.
应答机 C 模式，编码 5120。
Stopping squawk Charlie.
停止应答机 C 模式。
Affirm squawk 7500.
证实应答机 7500。
Altimeter 1003 8000ft.
高度表 1003，高度 8000 英尺。
Negative squawk ident due transponder failure.
应答机失效，无法识别。
Turn right heading 340.
右转航向 340。
Turn right 20 degrees.
右转 20 度。
Leave BK heading 190.
离开 BK，航向 190。
Fly heading 285.
航向飞 285。
Stop turn heading 070.
停止转弯，航向 070。
Request heading 180 due weather.
天气原因，请示航向 180。
Confirm danger area 113 active.
证实危险区域 113 有活动。
Your radar vector appears to be taking us to the prohibited area, confirm.
雷达引导好像把我们带入了禁飞区，证实。
50 miles right of track approved, when able, proceed direct TB.
可以右偏 50 海里，如可以，直飞 TB。
Indicated speed 270 knots.
指示空速 270 节。
Maintain 300 knots or less.
保持速度不大于 300 节。
Maintain 180 knots until 8 miles from touchdown.
保持 180 节直到离接地点 8 海里。
Maintain Mach decimal 82, transition speed 310 knots.
保持马赫数点 82，转换速度 310 节。
Maintain speed 280 knots or greater for separation.
因间隔，速度保持 280 节或更大。
Cross CK at 35 or later.
飞越 CK 台 35 分或之后。
Cross DG at 24 or earlier.
飞越 DG 台 24 分或之前。
Do not exceed 280 knots.
速度不要超过 280 节。
Reduce speed to 240 knots.
减速到 240 节。
Increase speed to 300 knots or greater.
加速到 300 节以上。
Increase speed by 10 knots.
速度增加 10 节。
Resume normal speed.
恢复正常速度。
No speed restrictions.
没有速度限制。
Request speed 200 knots due configuration.
构型原因，请示速度 200 节。
Request speed 250 knots due turbulence.
由于颠簸，请示速度 250 节。
Omit position reports until LN.
LN 前省略位置报。
Next report at IP.
下一报告点 IP。
Report required only at boundary.
只要求在交接点报告。
We have traffic at our 12 o’clock, 5 miles, 500 feet below, climbing.
活动飞机在 12 点钟方位，5 海里，500 英尺以下，上升。
Traffic indication at our 1 o’clock, 4 miles, same altitude, converging.
仪表显示活动飞机在 1 点钟方位，4 海里处，同高度，正在汇聚。
Request vectors.
请示引导。
Unable to receive transmission on that frequency.
那个频率不能收报。
Request 15 miles final.
请示五边 15 海里。
Maintain 3000 feet until glide path interception.
保持高度 3000 英尺，直到截获下滑道。
NOTAM says glide slope for Runway15 is unserviceable, confirm.
飞行员通告表明 15 跑道下滑道不工作，证实。
Confirm ILS frequency for Runway 17L.
证实跑道 17 左盲降频率。
In case of going around, turn left heading 210.
如复飞，左转航向 210。
Advise transponder capability.
请告知应答机可以模式。
Transponder Charlie.
应答机 C 模式。
Transponder unserviceable.
应答机不工作。
ADS-B transmitter 1090 (ten-ninety) data link.
ADS-B 发射机 1090 数据链。
ADS-B receiver 1090 (ten-ninety) data link.
ADS-B 接收机 1090 数据链。
Negative ADS-B.
没有 ADS-B。
Re-enter ADS-B aircraft identification.
重新输入 ADS-B 飞机识别码。
Stop ADS-B transmission.
停止 ADS-B 发射。
Stop squawk transmit ADS-B only.
停止应答机只发报 ADS-B。
Fly no further west of your current position.
当前位置不要再往西飞了。
Unable identify the waypoint, request radar vectors.
不能识别此航路点，请示雷达引导。
Right heading 120, my own terrain clearance.
右转航向 120，自行避让地形。
Heading 120, correction, 140.
航向 120，更正，140。
We are too low to the surrounding terrain. Confirm we are still being radar vectored.
我们高度太低，周围有地形。证实我们仍然雷达引导。
Confirm we are still above your minimum vectoring altitude.
证实我们仍然高于你们的最低引导高度。
Right heading 040 until passing FL70 then direct to BK.
右转航向 040，直到通过高度层 70，然后直飞 BK。
Direct to JO, descend to FL50.
直飞 JO，下降到高度层 50.
Passing FL70.
通过飞行高度层 70.
Descending to 4000 feet QNH1005, expect ILS approach Runway 24.
下降到 4000 英尺，修正海压 1005，预计盲降进近，跑道 24。
Request straight-in ILS approach Runway 24.
请示直接盲降进近，跑道 24。
Cleared straight-in ILS approach Runway 24, descend to 3000 feet, QNH1011.
可以直接盲降进近，跑道 24，下降到 3000 英尺，修正海压 1011。
Airfield in sight, request visual approach.
机场可见，请示目视进近。
When established on the localizer, descend on the glide path.
建立航向道后，沿下滑道下降。
Established on the localizer.
建立航向道。
Fully established Runway 24.
航向道下滑道截获，跑道 24。
Cleared VOR-DME approach Runway 24, descending to 3000 feet QNH1007.
准许 VOR/DME 进近，跑道 24，下降到修压 3000 英尺，修正海压 1007。
Runway in sight.
看见跑道。
Number One, contact Tower 118.7.
第一架，联系塔台 118.7。
Passing outer marker.
过外指点标。
Report MQR outbound.
MQR 背台报。
Procedure turn completed, localizer established.
程序转弯完成，航向道建立。
Request visual approach.
请示目视进近。
Cleared visual approach Runway 24.
可以目视进近，跑道 24。
Request holding instructions.
请示等待指令。
Hold over BKM VOR at FL100, inbound track 280 degrees, left hand pattern, outbound time 1 minute.
在 BKM VOR 台等待，高度层 100，向台航迹 280，左等待，出航时间 1 分钟。
Request holding procedure.
请示等待程序。
Hold on the 265 radial of BKM VOR between 25 and 30 miles DME, FL100, inbound track 085, right hand pattern, expected approach time 1022.
在 BKM VOR 台 265 度径向线，DME 距离 25 至 30 海里之间等待，高度层 100，向台航迹085，右等待，预计进近时间 1022.
Hold at 20 DME of ST VOR, FL100, inbound track 260 degrees, left turns, limiting outbounddistance 24 DME.
在 ST VOR 台 DME 20 海里等待，高度层 100，向台航迹 260，左等待，限制出航距离 DME24 海里。
Overhead YV, maintaining 3000 feet, entering hold.
飞越 YV，保持 3000 英尺，进入等待。
Leaving BKM VOR heading 110.
离开 BKM VOR 台，航向 110。
Leaving FL60, descending to 2500 feet, QNH1008.
离开高度层 60，下降到 2500 英尺，修正海压 1008.
Position 10 miles north east of LN.
当前位置 LN 东北方向 10 海里。
Turn right heading 180 for base leg.
右转航向 180，加入四边。
Reduce to minimum approach speed, turn right heading 230, cleared for ILS approach Runway 27.
降低到最小进近速度，右转航向 230，可以盲降进近，跑道 27。
No ATC speed restrictions. Contact Tower 118.9.
ATC 没有速度限制，联系塔台 118.9。
Three sixty turn left for delay.
由于延误，左转 360 度。
Continue present heading, expect through the localizer for spacing.
继续飞当前航向，由于间隔，预计穿过航向道。
Surveillance radar approach Runway 27, maintaining 2200 feet.
监视雷达进近，跑道 27，保持 2200 英尺。
QNH1003, threshold elevation 196 feet.
修正海压 1003，入口标高 196 英尺。
Precision radar approach Runway 27 heading 260, descending to 2500 feet, QNH1014.
精密雷达进近跑道 27，航向 260，下降到 2500 英尺，修正海压 1014。
Cleared to JEMMY via BK-1A Arrival.
可以经由 BK-1A 进场程序到 JEMMY。
Descend to reach 5000 feet by BK.
BK 点前下降高度到 5000 英尺。
When ready, descend to FL200. Report leaving FL300.
准备好时，下降到高度层 200。请示离开高度层 300。
Descend immediately FL250.
立即下降到高度层 250。
Descend to altitude 12000 feet QNH 1000.
下降到高度 12000 英尺，修正海压 1000。
Descend to height 2000 feet QFE 997 hectopascals.
下降到场压高 2000 英尺，场压 997 百帕。
Descend to 8000 feet at 1000 feet per minute or greater.
下降到 8000 英尺，下降率保持或大于 1000 英尺。
Maintain own separation and VMC, descend to FL50.
保持好自己的间隔和目视气象条件，下降到高度层 50。
Increasing rate of climb.
增加爬升率。
Unable expedite climb due weight.
由于重量，不能加快爬升。
Climb to 6000 feet, follow KODAP-01 Departure.
爬升到 6000 英尺，按 KODAP-01 号离场。
Passing altitude 2300 feet, climbing to FL80.
过高度 2300 英尺，爬升到高度层 80。
Climb to FL210, level restrictions of KODAP-01 Departure canceled.
爬升到高度层 210，取消 KODAP-01 号离场高度限制。
Climb to FL 210, cross AU at FL100 or below.
爬升到高度层 210，飞越 AU 时不高于高度层 100。
Climb to FL290, level at time 55.
爬升到高度层 290，55 分到达。
Unable FL390 by boundary, request FL330.
交接点之前不能到达高度层 390，请示高度层 330。
Descend to FL100, cross YU FL150 or above.
下降到高度层 100，通过 YU 时不低于高度层 150。
After passing North Cross, descend to FL150.
过了 North Cross，下降到高度层 150。
We are far above profile. Request holding.
我们太高了，请示等待。
Stop descent at 5000 feet.
5000 英尺停止下降。
Expedite descent until passing FL80.
快速下降通过高度层 80。
Expect descent after AK.
预计过 AK 后下降。
Continue approach Runway 36R, maintain visual separation with preceding traffic.
继续进近，跑道 36 右，与前机保持目视间隔。
Contact Control 80 miles after BK.
过 BK 80 海里处联系区调。
Request change to London Control.
请示换到伦敦管制频率。
Monitor Tower 118.1.
监听塔台频率 118.1。
Remain this frequency.
本频率长守。
We can see the approach lights at 200 feet.
200 英尺，我们能看到进近灯。
Cleared VOR approach Runway 36, followed by circling to Runway 18.
可以 VOR 进近，跑道 36，按照航图目视盘旋，跑道 18 落地。
Expect commencing approach at time 50.
预计开始进近时间 50 分。
Unable circling approach due company policy. Request diversion.
由于公司政策，不能盘旋进近。请示改航。
Request RNAV approach.
请示 RNAV 进近。
RNAV approach not available due FMS database. Request VOR approach.
由于 FMS 数据库原因，RNAV 不可用。请示 VOR 进近。
Cleared for LDA approach Runway 24.
可以 LDA 进近，跑道 24。
Unable RNAV due equipment, request conventional arrival.
设备原因，不能 RNAV 进近，请示传统方式进近。
Unable RNAV, loss of RAIM, request NDB approach.
RAIM 丢失，不能 RNAV 进近，请示 NDB 进近。
GPS primary lost, going around.
失去 GPS 主用，复飞了。
RAIM alert, going around.
RAIM 警告，复飞了。
Negative RNAV.
不能 RNAV 进近。
Proceed to AK, hold as published, expect approach clearance at 30.
直飞 AK，按航图等待，预计进近许可 30 分。
Request hold for weather improvement, visibility below company minima.
请示等待天气好转，能见度低于公司最低要求。
Hold at BKM VOR FL250, right hand pattern, expect further clearance at 23, landing delay at destination airport 30 minutes.
在 BKM VOR 台等待，高度层 250，右等待，预计进一步许可在 23 分，目的地机场着陆延误 30 分钟。
Holding northwest of W VOR FL120, what is the delay for approach?
W VOR 台西北等待，高度层 120，请问进近延误情况。
Request to extend the holding pattern for accomplishing the checklist.
请示延长等待以完成检查单。
Request extended holding to burn fuel to reduce the weight.
请示延长等待以便耗油减少重量。
Cleared for CAT II ILS approach Runway 24.
可以 II 类盲降进近，跑道 24。
Join right hand downwind, visual approach Runway 24.
加入右三边，目视进近，跑道 24。
Continue approach, prepare for possible go around.
继续进近，做好可能复飞的准备。
Disregard. We made the wrong transmission.
指令作废。我们报错了。
Roger, request continue approach.
明白，请示继续进近。
Stand by. We are carrying out procedures.
稍等。我们正在执行程序。
Wilco, words twice.
照办，发送两遍。
Maintaining FL350, expect descent after BKM VOR.
保持高度 350，预计过 BKM VOR 台后下降。
Climb to and maintain FL310. Maintain Mach number decimal 81 or greater until BKM VOR.
上升并保持高度层 310。BKM VOR 台前保持马赫数点 81 或更大。
Descend to and maintain FL 270. Do not exceed Mach number decimal 79.
下降到并保持高度层 270.不要超过马赫数点 79.
Continue climb to FL 290, cross BKM VOR not above FL 230.
继续爬升到高度层 290，飞越 BKM VOR 台不高于高度层 230。
Negative, unable cross BKM VOR at or above FL230 due performance.
不行，由于性能不能在飞越 BKM VOR 台时高于高度层 230.
Maintaining FL310 until advised.
保持高度层 310，等通知。
Descend to FL170, cross BKM VOR at or above FL210.
下降到高度层 170，飞越 BKM VOR 台时高于高度层 210。
Affirm, cross BKM VOR at or above FL190.
同意，飞越 BKM VOR 台时高于高度层 190。
Negative, unable to cross BKM VOR below FL170.
不行，飞越 BKM VOR 台时不能低于高度层 170.
Affirm, cross BKM VOR at or before 55.
同意，在 55 分或之前通过 BKM VOR 台。
Negative, unable to cross BKM VOR at 43 or later.
不行，不能在 43 分或之后通过 BKM VOR 台。
Request lose time en route due landing delay at destination airport.
由于目的地机场延误，请示航路上消耗时间。
Request lose time en route to finish the checklist.
请示航路消耗时间以完成检查单。
Request parallel offset from current track due weather ahead.
由于前方天气，请示平行偏置当前航迹。
Request parallel offset from current airway for 30 minutes due icing condition.
由于结冰条件，请示航路上平行偏执飞行 30 分钟。
Proceed offset 10 miles right of track until abeam BKM VOR.
右偏航迹 10 海里知道正切 BKM VOR 台。
Cleared offset 25 miles left of track for 30 minutes.
可以航迹左偏 25 海里飞 30 分钟。
Offset canceled, turn right to rejoin the A1 before BKM VOR.
取消偏置，BKM VOR 台前右转重新加入 A1。
Clear of weather, request to resume flight route.
已绕飞天气，请示回到航路。
Climb to and maintain FL290, re-cleared to track direct to BKM VOR, the rest unchanged.
上升到并保持高度层 290，重新直飞 BKM VOR 台，其余不变。
Estimating crossing LV NDB 1123.
预计 1123 飞越 LV NDB 台。
Passing POU at 43, maintaining FL310, estimating MLT at 55, next NLD.
当前位置 POU，43 分，高度层 310 保持，预计 MLT 55 分，下一点 NLD。
BKM 47, FL170 descending to FL120, abeam NLD VOR at 55.
BKM 47 分，高度层 170，下降到高度层 120，55 分正切 NLD VOR 台。
Report 25 miles from BKM VOR.
距离 BKM VOR 台 25 海里报。
Report 34 miles from Top of Descent.
距离下降顶点 34 海里报。
Report crossing 270 radial BKM VOR.
过 BKM VOR 台径向线 270 报。
Report 28 miles DME 210 radial BKM VOR.
BKM VOR 台 210 度径向线 28 海里报。
Climb to FL220, report passing FL170.
爬升到飞行高度层 220，通过高度层 170 报。
Descending immediately to FL190.
立即下降到高度层 190。
Leaving FL220 for FL190.
离开高度层 220，下降到高度层 190.
Request clearance to enter controlled airspace northeast of BKM VOR at FL240 at time 43.
请示在 BKM VOR 台西北方向高度 240，时间 43 分时进入管制空域的许可。
Remain outside controlled airspace, expect joining clearance at time 55.
还在管制空域外，预计 55 分进入。
Request to leave controlled airspace by descent.
请示通过下降离开管制空域。
Request to leave controlled airspace by climb.
请示通过爬升离开管制空域。
Descending to 5000 feet QNH 1014, report passing 7000 feet.
下降到 5000 英尺，修正海压 1014，过 7000 英尺报。
Request VMC descent to FL60.
请示目视气象条件下降到飞行高度层 60。
Descending to FL60, maintain VMC FL90 to FL70, report traffic in sight at FL80.
下降到高度层 60，高度层 90 到高度层 70 之间保持目视气象条件，高度层 80 看见活动飞机报告。
Request join airway A1 at DAPRO.
请示在 DAPRO 加入 A1 航路。
Cleared to destination airport via DAPRO, flight planned route, FL240, join A1 at FL240.
可以按计划放行通过 DAPRO 到目的地，飞行高度层 240，在高度层 240 加入 A1 航路。
Remain outside controlled airspace, expect further clearance at 55.
仍在管制空域外，预计 55 分有进一步许可。
If FL240 not available, we accept FL220.
如果高度层 240 不可用，我们接受高度层 220。
Cleared to leave A1 via BKM VOR, maintain FL230 while in controlled airspace.
可以经由 BKM VOR 台离开 A1，在管制空域保持高度 230。
Confirm we are under radar control.
证实我们在雷达管制区。
Confirm radar service is terminated.
证实雷达服务终止。
Radar service is terminated due technical failure. Maintain Mach number decimal 81 or less for separation.
由于技术故障雷达服务终止。保持马赫数点 81 或更小以保持间隔。
Confirm radar control is resumed.
证实雷达管制恢复。
Radar control is resumed, track direct to BKM VOR and increase speed to Mach number decimal 84.
雷达管制恢复，直飞 BKM VOR 台，增速到马赫数点 84.
Affirm RVSM.
可以 RVSM。
Negative RVSM due equipment downgraded.
设备降级，不可以 RVSM。
Request clearance into RVSM airspace.
请示进入 RVSM 空域许可。
Unable RVSM due turbulence.
由于颠簸不能 RVSM。
Ready to resume RVSM.
准备好，恢复 RVSM。
Position 42N（North）165E (East) at 0800, FL390, estimating 44 N 180E at 0900 45N 170W next.
当前位置北纬 42 度，东经 165 度，时间 0800，高度层 390，预计到达北纬 44 度、东经180 度时间 0900，下一位置北纬 45 度、西经 170 度。
At 150W (west) contact San Francisco Radio, primary 3494, secondary 11342.
在西经 150 度联系旧金山，主用 3494，备用 11342。
At 144E (east) squawk 2000.
东经 144 度时，应答机换 2000。
CPDLC connected.
CPDLC（control-pilot data link communication）已连接。
Continue CPDLC make position report via CPDLC.
继续 CPDLC，由 CPDLC 做位置报。
SELCAL CODE EFFG, request SELCAL check.
选择呼叫代码 EFFG，请示选呼检查。
CPDLC unserviceable, request to revert to voice communication.
CPDLC 不工作，请示恢复语音通讯。
The air conditioning system has malfunctioned.
空调系统已故障。
We have only one air conditioning pack operational. Request a new cruising level below FL300.
我们仅有一个空调组件工作，请示低于高度层 300 的新巡航高度。
All our air conditioning packs have malfunctioned. Request rapid descent to MEA .
所有空调组件已经故障，请示立即下降到最低航路高度。
We had a malfunction of one air conditioning pack. Request descent to a lower level.
一个空调组件故障，请示下降到低高度。
We have lost electrical power to the cabin air compressor. Request immediate descent to 10,000 feet.
客舱空气压缩机失去电源，请示立即下降到 10000 英尺。
We just had a smoke emergency. We need to depressurize the airplane to let in fresh air. Request rapid descent to 8000 feet.
我们刚出现了烟雾紧急情况，需要释压让新鲜空气进入。请示快速下降到 8000 英尺。
We have unusual smell from air conditioning packs. Request stop climb at 7000 feet.
空调组件出现异常气味，请示保持 7000 英尺，停止爬升。
Many passengers are suffering from smoke inhalation. Request medical assistance on arrival.
许多乘客吸入烟尘，请示到达时医疗救助。
Our pressurization system has malfunctioned.
增压系统故障。
We have difficulty in controlling the cabin pressure.
我们控制座舱压力有困难。
We have a cabin altitude problem.
座舱高度有问题
Our cabin rate of climb has red-lined. Request immediate descent.
座舱爬升率达到红线，请示立即下降。
We have a slow cabin decompression. Request immediate descent.
座舱缓慢释压，请示立即下降。
Our cabin altitude at one time had reached 16000 feet. Some passengers have symptoms of hypoxia.
座舱高度一度高达 16000 英尺，部分乘客出现缺氧症状。
We are now depressurized and will fly a more shallow descent profile.
我们现在正在释压，需要更平缓的下降剖面。
Request descent rate less than 500 feet per minute due to unpressurized cabin.
由于客舱释压，请示下降率小于 500 英尺每分钟。
We are now ventilating with ram air. It is best that our rate of descent does not exceed 600 feet per minute.
我们现在通过冲压空气通风，下降率最好不超过 600 英尺每分钟。
We have a problem with the avionics ventilation system.
电子通风系统有问题。
We have an avionics ventilation problem. The skin heat-exchangers and blower fan have failed.
电子通风系统有问题。蒙皮热交换器和鼓风机有故障。
The avionics ventilation is unserviceable. Request diversion to the closest suitable airport.
电子通风不可用，请示备降到最近合适的机场。
We have severe vibration coming from the avionics ventilation fan.
电子通风风扇有严重的抖振。
There are unusual noises coming from the avionics bay.
电子设备舱有异常噪音。
Our FMS has malfunctioned. Request radar vectors.
飞行管理系统故障，请示雷达引导。
Request further climb due wind-shear.
由于风切变，请示进一步爬升。
Unable to maintain altitude, request leaving RVSM airspace.
不能保持高度，请示离开 RVSM 空域。
We cannot make RNP approach due equipment.
由于没有设备，我们不能使用 RNP 进近。
Our navigation accuracy is low. Request to climb to minimum safe altitude.
导航精度低，请示爬升到最低安全高度。
We have a navigation map shift, unable to perform the RNAV approach. Request radar vectors.
导航地图有偏移，不能使用 RNVA 进近，请示雷达引导。
Inertial reference system has failed. We are navigating on raw data. Request conventional approach.
惯性导航系统失效了，我们在使用原始导航。请示传统进近。
The Morse code for the VOR is different from the approach chart. Confirm the VOR is fully operational.
VOR 台莫尔斯码与进近图上的不一致。证实 VOR 台正常运行中。
The ILS signal seems to be very unstable. Did any other pilot report a similar situation?
盲降系统信号很不稳定。其他飞行员有报告类似情况吗？
The approach lights for Runway 36L are a bit different from those shown on the airport diagram.
36 左跑道进近灯与机场图上的现实有点不同。
The flight path is unstable. Going around.
（下降）飞行轨迹不稳定，复飞了。
We made a missed approach due to unstable ILS signals.
由于不稳定盲降信号，我们复飞了。
The ILS signal was unstable. Request approach to another runway or request another type of approach.
盲降信号不稳定，请示使用另一条跑道进近，或请示另一种进近方式。
The DME indication is not correct. Confirm the DME is still in service.
DME 显示不正确，证实 DME 还在正常工作中。
We have lost our flight plan after a flight management computer reset.
我们复位了飞行管理计算机后丢失了飞行计划。
We need a few minutes to reprogram the flight management computers. Request radar vectors.
我们需要几分钟重新输入飞行管理计算机，请示雷达引导。
We need to reconfigure the flight management computers for approach. Request holding instructions.
我们需要为进近重新设置飞行管理计算机，请示等待指令。
We are now flying with basic navigation due to systems failure. Request radar vectors.
由于系统失效，我们现在使用基本导航，请示雷达引导。
We have multiple failures on the inertial reference system. We are no longer able to fly oceanic route. Request return for landing.
惯导系统有多个失效，我们不能再飞跨洋航线，请示返场着陆。
We do not meet GPS approach requirement due to flight crew qualifications.
由于机组资质，我们不能满足 GPS 进近要求。
Our Airline policy does not allow us to perform CAT IIIC approach.
航空公司政策不允许我们执行 IIIC 类进近。
Our operations manual forbids this procedure.
我们的运行手册禁止此程序。
Our Aviation Authority does not permit this procedure.
航空当局不允许此程序。
We are unable to conform to the noise abatement procedure due performance.
由于性能，我们不能遵守降噪程序。
We are not qualified for CAT IIIB approach and auto-land. Request diversion.
我们不具备 IIIB 类进近和自动落地资格，请示改航。
Our VHF number One receiver has failed. We are no longer monitoring 121.5.
我们第一部甚高频接收机失效了，我们不再监听 121.5.
All stations, transmitting blind due to receiver failure.
各台注意，由于接收机失效，正在盲发。
All of our VHF transmitters have failed, now transmitting on HF radio. Please respond.
我们所有的甚高频发射机都失效了，现在使用高频无线电发报，请示回复。
Our SELCAL has malfunctioned. We will continue monitoring your frequency.
选择呼叫失效了，我们会继续坚挺频率。
We are receiving an ELT signal on 121.5.
我们在 121.5 上收到了紧急定位发射机信号。
We are picking up a broadcast signal on 121.5.
我们在 121.5 上收到了广播信号。
Our satellite phone is unserviceable. We are unable to call company operations.
卫星电话不工作，我们联系不上公司。
Our data-link has malfunctioned. Request re-release the flight plan by voice.
数据链路故障了，请示口述放行飞行计划。
Our data-link has malfunctioned. Request ATC clearance by voice.
数据链路故障了，请示口述 ATC 放行许可。
My apologies, I wasn’t aware the boom mike was transmitting.
不好意思，我没发觉话筒在发射。
Sorry for blocking the frequency due microphone jammed.
抱歉由于麦克风卡阻堵塞了通信频率。
We have an electrical failure.
我们有一个电气故障。
One of our generators has failed. At present moment, we are still able to continue to our destination.
一部发电机失效率，现在我们还能继续飞往目的地。
Request diversion to the nearest suitable airport due AC BUS failure.
交流汇流条失效，请示备降到最近合适的机场。
We are not supplying power to our DC BUS. Request priority landing.
我们不能再为交流汇流条供电，请示优先着陆。
We have a problem with the aircraft battery. Request priority landing.
飞机电瓶有问题，请示优先着陆。
One of our transformers has failed. I’ll let you know if a diversion is required.
一部发射机失效了，如果需要备降，我会第一时间告诉你。
Electrical system has a serious malfunction. Request radar vectors to an airport that’s within 20 minutes off light time.
电子系统严重故障，请示雷达引导到 20 分钟以内能够飞到的机场。
We are operating with only the emergency generator. Request track direct to final, Runway 26.
我们能够使用的只有紧急发电机，请示直飞 26 跑道五边。
We are flying with batteries only. Is there any airport available within 25 minutes of flying?
我们仅靠电瓶飞行。有没有 25 分钟以内能够飞到的可用机场？
If there is no airport within 100 miles, we have to make a forced landing.
如果 100 海里范围内没有机场，我们必须迫降。
We have less than 10 minutes of battery power left. We are preparing for ditching procedure.
我们只剩不足 10 分钟的电量，正在准备水上迫降程序。
We have switched off most of our electrical systems for smoke procedure. Request vectors for a long final, Runway 15.
为了排烟程序，我们关掉了大部分电气系统。请示雷达引导到 15 跑道长五边。
We have cut off the electrical system to the cabin and the onboard fire is under control.
我们已经切断了通往客舱的电气系统，机上火情得到了控制。
We had an electrical fire from the galley, now extinguished. Request return to land.
厨房有电气火警，现在已经熄灭。请示返场着陆。
There was a fire from the avionics bay. Request radar vectors for final.
电子设备舱有火警，请示雷达引导到五边。
We have had a bird strike. Our windshield has cracked.
我们遭遇鸟击，风挡出现裂痕。
The windshield suddenly had electrical arcing. We need to pull the circuit breakers and delay the approach.
风挡突然出现电弧，我们需要拔出跳开关，推迟进近。
The cockpit side window is not sealed properly. Request reduce to minimum speed and descend to 4000 feet.
驾驶舱侧窗没有关好，请示减速到最小速度，下降到 4000 英尺。
We had to go around due pilot seat moving. We’ll try to reset the circuit breaker before making another approach.
驾驶员座椅移动，我们刚才必须复飞。我们试着重置座椅电路跳开关后再进近。
We have already discharged the engine extinguishers. The fire warning light is still on. Do you have a visual on our left engine?
我们已经使用了发动机灭火瓶，火警等仍然亮着。你们能看到我们的左发有火吗
We cannot extinguish the engine fire. Request priority landing and emergency services on arrival.
我们不能熄灭发动机火情，请示优先着陆和到场时的紧急服务。
We have an APU fire warning. Can you verify if there is smoke coming from the back of the plane?
我们有 APU 火警。你能否看到我们飞机后部有烟？
The APU fire seems to be extinguished. Request fire trucks on standby and stairs vehicle to disembark the passengers.
APU 火情看样子被熄灭了。请示消防车和客梯车，以便乘客下机。
The APU is still on fire. We are evacuating. Request emergency services.
APU 仍在着火，我们正在紧急疏散，请示紧急服务。
We had a cargo smoke warning. Advise the ground handlers NOT to open our cargo door until the passengers have all disembarked.
我们出现了货舱烟雾警告。请告知地面装卸人员在所有乘客下机前千万别打开货舱门。
A passenger ignited the lavatory waste bin. Advise the airport police to await our arrival.
一名乘客点燃了盥洗室垃圾箱。告知机场警察到场处理。
We have smoke coming out of our avionics bay. It is out of control. Request proceed direct to final and cancel all speed restrictions.
有烟从电子设备舱冒出，已经失控了，请示直飞五边并取消所有速度限制。
We have smoke coming from our avionics bay. We are evacuating. Request fire trucks.
有烟从电子设备舱冒出，我们正在疏散，请示消防车。
We have smoke coming from our avionics bay. We are disembarking the passengers.
有烟从电子设备舱冒出，我们正在让乘客下机。
Request descent to 10000 feet to ventilate the aircraft due smoke.
有烟，请示下降到 10000 英尺，使飞机通风。
We had emptied most of our fire extinguishers, but the cabin fire is still on.
我们已经放空了大部分灭火瓶，但是客舱火情仍然存在。
We are having flight control problems.
我们有飞机操纵问题。
Our flight control computers are not functioning well. We are having difficulty maintaining level flight, unable RVSM.
飞行控制计算机工作不太理想，保持平飞有困难，不能再 RVSM 空域飞行。
Our pitch control has malfunctioned. We cannot move the elevators. We are flying the airplane with only trim.
俯仰控制失效了，升降舵动不了，我们正在只用配平来控制飞机。
The aircraft has a tendency to roll to the right. I need additional airspace to maneuver.
飞机有向右横滚的趋势，我需要更多的空域机动。
We have finished the checklist but still cannot retract some of the speed brakes. Request the longest runway for landing.
我们已经完成了检查单，但还是不能收回一些减速板，请示最长跑道落地。
We cannot fully extend the flaps. Request the longest runway for landing.
我们不能全放襟翼，请示最长跑道落地。
We have asymmetric flaps. Airplane is rolling to the left. Request holding to solve the problem.
襟翼位置不对称，飞机正向左横滚，请示等待解决故障。
Request high speed approach. Part of our flight control surfaces have separated from the wing.
请示大速度进近。部分飞行操纵面与机翼分离。
Request immediate climb above the minimum safe altitude to perform the checklist due to run-away trim condition.
由于配平失控，请示立即上安全高度以上做检查单。
Request vectors for long final. We are controlling the airplane with mechanical backup.
请示雷达引导到长五边。我们正在用机械备用系统控制飞机。
Request return to FL250.We just had an air-upset situation and lost a lot of altitude.
请示回到高度层 250。刚才空中姿态有异常，并且掉了很多高度。
We have a problem with yaw damping. The aircraft is oscillating severely. Request diversion.
偏航阻尼器出现问题，飞机摇摆很严重，请示备降。
We have lost electrical power to some of the flight control actuators. Request delay ourdescent to perform checklist.
一些飞行操纵作动筒失去了电源，请示推迟下降来做检查单。
Some of our fuel pumps have low pressure. Request descent.
一些燃油泵低压，请示下降。
We have a problem with fuel temperature. Request holding position on the taxiway.
燃油温度有问题，请示滑行道上原地等待。
We are leaking fuel slowly. Request diversion.
燃油慢速泄露，请示备降。
We have a severe fuel leak situation, unable to reach the closest airport. You can expect us to make a forced landing near our present location.
燃油严重泄漏，无法抵达最近机场。估计会在当前文职附近紧急迫降。
Our cabin crew reports that we have fuel leak from the right wing. Request diversion to closest suitable airport.
客舱机组报告说右机翼漏油，请示备降到最近合适的机场。
We have already shut down engine Number One, but it is still leaking fuel near the pylon. Request emergency services.
一发已经关车，但是发动机吊架附近仍然在漏油，请示紧急服务。
The ground crew reports that we are leaking a bit of fuel from the bottom of the right engine nacelle. We are delaying taxi.
地面人员报告说右发吊舱下面漏油，我们推迟滑行。
We need to continue to run the engines at our present location for a few minutes, will advise you shortly.
我们需要在当前位置让发动机运转一会儿，很快告知。
The ground crew reports that we are leaking a significant amount of fuel from the bottom of Number Three engine. We have just shut it down.
地面人员报告三发下面漏油严重，我们刚刚将它关车了。
The fuel leak has stopped. But if a fire starts at any time, I will order an evacuation.
漏油停止了，但一旦有火警，我都会组织疏散撤离。
We have leaked a large amount of fuel onto the apron. Request fire trucks on standby and the stairs vehicle to disembark the passengers.
有大量的燃油漏在了机坪上，请示消防车待命、客梯车让乘客下机。
We might have a fuel leak near the wing root. Request fire trucks on arrival.
翼根可能漏油，请示消防车到场。
We have fumes in the cabin, possibly due to a fuel leak. We are anticipating an immediate evacuation after landing.
客舱有烟味，可能是漏油了。预计会在落地后立即撤离。
We are evacuating. Advise emergency personnel that fuel odors are still present in the cabin.
我们正在紧急疏散。请告知地面人员客舱仍有燃油味道。
We are too heavy for landing. Request fuel-dump at the fuel dumping area.
落地重量太重，请示到放油区放油。
Request climb for dumping fuel and vectors to the fuel dump zone.
请示上升高度放油，请示雷达引导到放油区。
We need about 18 minutes to jettison fuel before coming in for the approach.
我们在进近前需要大概 18 分钟放油。
We cannot shut off the fuel dump valve. Request radar vectors for short final, Runway 17.
我们无法关断放油活门，请示雷达引导到 17 跑道短五边。
We are indicating fuel filter clog. Request descent and to maintain high speed.
燃油过滤显示堵塞，请示下降并保持大速度。
Our left engine failed due to fuel starvation.
没有燃油供应，左发失效。
We are near the freezing temperature of jet fuel. Request descent to FL 390.
我们接近燃油的冰点温度，请示下降到高度层 390.
We suspect there is contamination in our fuel tanks.
我们怀疑燃油油箱有污染物。
One of our hydraulic systems has exceeded temperature limits.
一个液压系统超温。
We have shut down one of the hydraulic systems.
我们已经关掉了其中一个液压系统。
The backup hydraulic system is operational but we still want to divert.
备用液压系统在工作，但我们仍想备降。
Our hydraulic systems have a malfunction. Request descent to lower levels to extend flaps in advance.
液压系统故障，请示下降到低高度以便提前放襟翼。
Our hydraulic fluid is dangerously low, possibly due to a leak. Request descent to lower levels to extend flaps.
液压油低得可怕，可能是漏油。请示下降到低高度放出襟翼。
Two of our hydraulic systems have failed. Request immediate diversion.
两个液压系统失效，请示立即备降。
Our ram air turbine is not providing any hydraulic pressure. We are still operating on one hydraulic system only. Request diversion to the nearest suitable airport.
冲压空气涡轮没有提供任何液压压力。我们仍然可以使用一个液压系统，请示备降到最近合适的机场。
Request the longest runway and vectors for a wide downwind due to hydraulic failure.
由于液压失效，请示最长跑道和雷达引导到宽的三边。
We still have only one hydraulic system. Request the longest runway for landing.
我们仍然有一套液压系统，请示最长跑道着陆。
Our left engine anti-ice system has failed. Request immediate climb to leave the icing area.
左发防冰系统失效，请示立即爬升离开结冰区。
We must descend immediately to exit icing conditions. Our right engine bleed air has failed.
我们必须立即下降离开结冰条件。右发引气已经失效。
Both our windshield heating systems have failed. Ice is obstructing our view. Request latest airport weather.
两部风挡加温系统都已失效。冰挡住了我们的视线，请示最新的机场天气。
We had electrical arcing on the windshield and pulled the circuit breakers according to the checklist. Will advise when ready for approach.
风挡刚才有电弧，根据检查单，我们已经拔出电路跳开关。我们准备好进近时将告知。
We performed the missed approach because my windshield wiper became inoperative and I could not see very well.
我们执行了复飞是因为风挡雨刷不能用来，我无法看清楚。
Our pitot static heating system has failed. We might have an altitude error.
皮托管静压加温系统失效，我们可能有高度误差。
We made the overshoot because of a stall warning, probably caused by a defective angle of attack probe.
我们复飞是因为失速告警，可能是由于迎角探头误报。
I had to abort takeoff because I didn’t receive any airspeed indication.
我必须中断起飞，因为我没有看到任何空速指示。
We have an error in our airspeed. Request to climb to minimum safe altitude.
空速有误差，请示爬升到最低安全高度。
We have master warning lights in the cockpit. Request landing at the nearest suitable airport.
驾驶舱主警告灯亮了，请示就近合适机场着陆。
We have a master caution. I will notify you if a diversion is required.
有一个主警示灯亮了，如需备降，我将告知。
Some of our instruments are not indicating correctly. Request level off to perform checklist.
一些仪表显示不正确，请示改平做检查单。
Two of our display units have failed. We are no longer RNP qualified. Request diversion.
我们的两个显示屏失效，我们不再具备 RNP 资格，请示备降。
We made the go around due to navigation accuracy downgrade.
我们复飞是因为导航精度降级。
We made the go around due to FMS position error.
我们复飞是因为飞行管理系统位置误差。
We made the go around due to map drift on our navigation display.
我们复飞是因为导航显示上地图漂移。
We made the go around due to GPS error.
我们复飞是因为 GPS 误差。
We made the go around due to lateral deviation exceedance.
我们复飞是因为横向偏离超限。
We made the go around due to CDU failure.
我们复飞是因为 CDU 失效。
We made the go around because we exceeded the vertical deviation limit.
我们复飞是因为我们超出了纵向偏离限制。
We no longer have altitude warning. Request leaving RVSM airspace.
我们不再具备高度偏离警告，请示离开 RVSM 空域。
We have autopilot disconnection. We are no longer RVSM qualified. Request leaving RVSM airspace.
自动驾驶脱开了，我们不再符合 RVSM 资质，请示离开 RVSM 空域。
Our landing capability has degraded. Request terminate our approach.
着陆类别降低，请示终止进近。
Request to climb to minimum safe altitude due to malfunction of navigation computers.
由于导航计算机故障，请示爬升到最低安全高度。
We performed the go-around because we had a ground proximity warning.
我们复飞是因为近地警告。
We have conflicting traffic at one o’clock, 6 miles, descending. Request heading 130 for avoidance.
1 点钟方位，6 海里处有下降的冲突飞机，请示飞航向 130 躲避。
We have conflicting traffic at eleven o’clock, 8 miles, climbing. Request vectors for avoidance.
11 点钟方位，8 海里处，有冲突飞机正在爬升，请示雷达引导躲避。
Traffic at our twelve o’clock, 10 miles, climbing. Should we expedite our descent to cross altitudes?
冲突飞机在我们 12 点钟方位，10 海里处，正在上升。我们应该加速下降以穿越高度吗？
Unable, TCAS RA.
不能，TCAS RA。
We are clear of conflict. Request further instructions.
我们解除冲突了。请示进一步指令。
About twenty passengers and crew members were injured during the TCAS maneuver. Request diversion and medical assistance on arrival.
大约 20 名乘客和机组人员在做机动飞行时受伤了。请示备降和医疗援助到场。
We are having abnormal engine indications. Request to reduce speed to 250 knots.
我们显示不正常的发动机参数。请示调速到 250 节。
Our engine parameters are unstable. Request stop climb at FL220.
我们的发动机参数不稳定。请示在高度层 220 时停止爬升。
Our oil pressure reading is lower than normal. Request hold at present position.
我们滑油压力度数比正常要低，请示在当前位置等待。
The oil temperature is higher than normal. We are monitoring other engine parameters.
滑油温度比正常的要高，我们正在监控其他发动机参数。
Engine indicates high EGT at idle power setting. We need to have partial thrust in the descent. Request an early descent.
发动机指示在油门慢车时显示 EGT 较高。我们需要带部分推力下降。请示提前下降。
We are reading high engine vibration. Request to delay takeoff.
发动机度数有较高的抖振，请示推迟起飞。
Cabin altitude is increasing abnormally. Request to level off.
客舱高度指示增加异常，请示改平飞。
Our instruments indicate excessive high cabin altitude.
我们的仪表显示客舱高度过高。
Our instrument indicates abnormal cabin pressure differential.
仪表显示不正常的客舱压差。
Our fuel endurance is 48 minutes. We must leave the hold otherwise we will be at minimum fuel.
我们的燃油续航时间是 48 分钟。我们必须退出等待，否则我们将出现最低燃油。
Cockpit oxygen cylinder pressure is low. Request to return for landing.
驾驶舱氧气瓶压力低，请示返场着陆。
We are holding at present position. It appears one of the over-wing exits has unlocked.
我们在原地等待。好像机翼上方的一个出口没锁。
It seems some of the spoilers cannot be retracted. We have to recalculate our landing distance before we start our approach, standby.
似乎一部分扰流板不能收回。我们需要重新计算一下着陆距离才能进近，稍等。
We have an indication that the nose wheel did not extend properly. Request low pass for visual check
仪表显示前轮没有正常放轮，请示低空通场目视检查。
We have lost our braking. We used thrust reversers to stop the aircraft. Request ground services to chock the nose wheel.
我们失去了刹车，刚才使用反推来停住飞机，请示地面服务用销子挡好前轮。
Our brakes have seized. The tyres might burst during touchdown. Request fire trucks on arrival.
我们的刹车卡死了。可能接地时轮胎会发生爆胎，请示消防车到场。
We made the go-around because our landing gear wouldn't extend normally. Request holding pattern to perform checklist.
我们刚才复飞的原因是起落架无法正常释放，请示等待做检查单。
We have exhausted all options. We will land without the nose gear fully locked.
我们用尽了所有办法。现在只能够尝试没有前起落架完全锁住的情况下落地。
We cannot extend the left landing gear. Request foaming the runway.
我们不能放出左起落架，请示在跑道上喷洒泡沫。
Request diversion to a nearby airport with foaming capability.
请示备降到附近一个能够喷洒防火泡沫的机场。
We applied maximum braking when we rejected takeoff. Request fire services to escort the aircraft back to the apron.
刚才中断起飞时我们使用了最大刹车，请示消防车护送飞机回停机坪。
The tyres are deflated. We will have to hold at present position for maintenance inspection.
轮胎瘪了，我们需要原地等待机务来做检查。
I think we blew a nose wheel tyre. Request holding position.
我想我们的前轮爆胎了，请示原地等待。
We no longer have airspeed and altitude on our primary displays.
我们的主显示器不再有空速和高度显示。
We have errors with our navigation. Request radar monitoring.
我们的导航有误差，请示雷达监控。
Our inertial reference system has failed, unable GPS approach. Request ILS or VOR approach.
我们的惯性导航系统失效了，不能够使用 GPS 进近，请示盲降或 VOR 进近。
We made the go around because the GPWS warning was triggered.
我们复飞是因为触发了近地警告。
We have to recalibrate our instruments. Request to level off and maintain heading.
我们必须重新校准仪表，请示改平飞并保持当前航向。
Our ADS-B transmitter appears to be malfunctioning. Terminating further ADS-B transmissions.
我们的 ADS-B 发报机似乎故障了，终止 ADS-B 发报。
ADS-B equipment degradation, will advise when able to resume operations.
ADS-B 设备降级，恢复使用时告知。
GPS unreliable, terminating ADS-B transmissions.
GPS 不可靠，终止 ADS-B 发报。
Our ADS-B has malfunctioned. Is there any weather advisory at our destination?
我们的 ADS-B 发报机已故障。有目的地机场的气象报吗？
We made an overshoot because our ADS-B indicated a possible runway incursion.
我们复飞是因为我们的 ADS-B 显示可能有跑道入侵。
We made a go-around due to head-up display problem. We’ll inform you when we are ready for the approach.
我们复飞是因为屏显故障。准备好进近是我们将通知你们。
Our airspeed is unreliable. Request climb to minimum safe altitude to perform checklist.
我们的空速指示不可靠，请示爬升到最低安全高度左检查单。
Our airspeed is unreliable. Request radar vectors for long final.
我们的空速指示不可靠，请示雷达引导到长五边
We made the go-around because the radio altimeter triggered flare mode.
我们复飞的原因是因为无线电高度表触发了拉平模式。
Our weather radar has failed and we are in IMC. Request return for landing.
我们的气象雷达失效，我们在仪表气象条件下飞行，请示返场着陆。
Our weather radar has malfunctioned. What is the highest available level for cruise?
我们的气象雷达故障。最高可用的巡航高度是多少？
Our weather radar has failed. How did the preceding aircraft deviate from the weather?
我们的气象雷达坏了。前机怎么绕飞天气的？
We do not have that route in our database. Which heading should we maintain for now？
我们数据库没有这个航路。我们现在应该保持哪个航向？
We do not have that runway in our database. Request delay our descent while we program the CDU.
我们数据库中没有这条跑道。我们需要输入 CDU，请示推迟下降。
We have a navigation malfunction. Request diversion to a suitable airport that has less complex terrain.
我们的导航故障，请示备降到就近、有较少复杂地形的机场。
Our oxygen pressure is dropping rapidly. Request to fly heading 050 and descent to FL180 to escape from the mountainous area.
我们的氧气压力快速下降，请示飞航向 050，下降到高度层 180 以避开山区。
The NOTAM says the ILS is unserviceable, but we are still picking up the Morse Code, confirm it is still in operation.
航行通告说盲降不工作，但我们仍然收到了莫尔斯代码，证实一下盲降仍然可用。
We have an engine failure. Following ETOPS procedure, request descent to FL200, maintain high speed and proceed direct to alternate airport.
我们的发动机故障了。按照 ETOPS 程序，请示下降到高度层 200，保持大速度直飞备降场。
We cannot provide oxygen to the passengers as we are not sure where the smoke is coming from.
我们不能给乘客供氧，因为我们不确定烟雾来源。
Many passengers have suffered from smoke inhalation. Request medical services.
许多乘客已经吸入了烟雾，请示医疗服务。
There was heavy smoke in the cabin before we ventilated the aircraft. Request medical assistance for passengers after landing.
我们给飞机通风前有浓烟，请示落地后给乘客医疗救助。
The aircraft is depressurized. We are descending. Confirm 10,000 feet is enough to clear terrain until we reach our alternate.
飞机在释压，我们正在下降。证实到达备降场前 10000 英尺能否满足越障。
We are no longer getting bleed air from the right engine. Request immediate descent to leave the icing area.
我们没有来自右发的引气，请示立即下降到结冰区。
Our APU bleed air malfunctioned during engine startup. We are calling the ground staff,standby.
我们的 APU 引气在发动机开车时故障了。我们正在呼叫地面服务，请稍等。
We are expediting descent to enable a windmill startup. Request further descent.
为了能够风转启动发动机，我们正在加速下降，请示进一步下降。
We are unable to restart engine number one with bleed air. Request high speed for a windmill air start.
我们不能用引气启动一发，请示大速度风转启动。
Both engine bleed air systems have failed and we are relying on APU bleed for air conditioning. Request descent to 14, 000 feet.
发动机引气系统全部失效，现在依靠 APU 引气来提供空调，请示下降到 14000 英尺
We have no bleed air coming from either engines or APU. Request rapid descent to 10,000feet.
我们没有任何来自发动机或 APU 的引气，请示快速下降到 10000 英尺。
We are leaking bleed air. Request turn right heading 095 to avoid the icing area.
我们的阴气正在泄露，请示右转飞航向 095 以避开结冰区。
CPDLC has malfunctioned. We are reverting to voice communication.
CPDLC 失效，我们正在恢复语音通信。
Disregard my last CPDLC request for climb. We have a system problem and will maintain present level for now.
作废上次 CPDLC 上升请示。我们出现了系统问题，现在将保持当前高度。
CPDLC terminated due to failure, reverting to voice communication.
由于故障，终止 CPDLC，恢复语音通信。
We just had an APU fire warning, and discharged the fire extinguisher, Request visual check if there is smoke coming from our tail section.
我们刚刚有过火警，也释放了灭火瓶，请示目视检查飞机尾部是否有烟雾。
Another aircraft has seen a lot of smoke coming from our APU. We are evacuating. Request emergency services.
另一架飞机看到我们 APU 区域有很多烟雾冒出。我们正在紧急撤离，请示紧急服务。
We are at bay15. We have an APU fire. Request fire services.
我们在 15 号机位，有 APU 火警，请示灭火服务。
We have a generator failure and cannot start our APU at this altitude. Request descent to perform APU startup.
我们有一部发电机故障，在这个高度不能启动 APU，请示下降重启 APU。
A passenger has opened an over-wing emergency exit. The slide has deployed. Request to cancel our slot time.
一名乘客打开了机翼紧急出口，滑梯已经放出。请示取消立场时间。
A passenger tried to unlock the cabin door in flight, the cabin crew restrained him. Request airport police on arrival.
一名乘客企图在空中打开客舱门，客舱机组已经将他制服，请示落地后机场警察到场。
We have an abnormal noise coming from one of our cabin doors. Request rapid descent to 5000 feet.
客舱门有异常噪音，请示快速下降到 5000 英尺。
Smoke is coming from the cabin floor. We are performing an evacuation. All slides have been deployed.
烟雾从客舱门冒出，我们正在紧急撤离，所有滑梯已经放出。
We had a smoke warning from the forward cargo hold. We are evacuating.
前货舱有烟雾警告，我们正在撤离。
We have a cargo smoke warning. We are disembarking passengers. Request fire services.
货舱烟雾警告，我们正在让乘客下机，请示消防服务。
We have smoke coming from our avionics bay. Advise the fire fighters that it might be an electrical fire.
电子设备舱有烟雾，请告诉消防员可能是电气火情。
The cockpit windshield has cracked. Request descent to FL220.
驾驶舱风挡裂了，请示下降到高度层 220.
The windshield is cracked on the outside. Request descent.
风挡外层裂了，请示下降。
Neither of us can see through our windshield. Does your airport permit auto-land?
我们都无法通过风挡看到，你们机场允许自动着陆吗？
Our thrust lever is not responsive. We cannot reduce thrust on engine Number One. Request holding.
推力手柄没有反应，我们不能降低一发推力，请示等待。
Our engine control has malfunctioned. We cannot get much thrust. Request immediate descent.
发动机控制故障了，我们不能获得较大推力，请示立即下降。
We have a thrust reverser opened in flight. We cannot maintain this level. Request immediate descent.
空中反推被打开，我们无法保持当前高度，请示立即下降。
We still cannot retract the thrust reverser. Our approach speed will be higher than normal. Request vectors for the longest Runway.
我们仍然不能收回反推，我们的进近速度会大于正常速度，请示雷达引导到最长的跑道落地。
We aborted takeoff due loss of engine oil pressure.
由于发动机失去了滑油压力，我们中断起飞了。
We have an engine oil leak. Request diversion.
发动机滑油泄露，请示备降。
We have a low oil pressure warning from engine Number Two. Request diversion.
二发出现低滑油压力告警，请示备降。
Engine Number One has a temperature problem. Request holding to perform checklist.
一发温度有问题，请示等待做检查单。
Our EGT continues to be above the maximum limit. Request descent. We might shut down engine Number Two shortly.
排气温度继续高于最大限制，请示下降。我们可能马上关掉二发。
We have performed our procedures but engine vibration still exists. Request diversion.
我们已经完成了程序，但是发动机抖振仍然存在，请示备降。
The engine vibration is now causing the airplane to shake violently. We are shutting down our engine Number Three.
现在发动机抖振引起飞机震动剧烈。我们正关掉三发。
We’ve made a visual inspection of engine Number Two from the cabin. The engine cowling has fallen off.
我们从客舱里目视观察了二发，其整流罩脱落了。
Engine Number Three has smoke coming out of the pylon section. We are evacuating.
三发吊架部分出现烟雾。我们正在撤离。
Ground vehicle has collided with our engine nacelle. Maintenance work is needed before flight. Request cancel our airway clearance.
地面车辆碰到了发动机吊舱，飞行前需要机务维修，请示取消我们的航路许可。
The Number Two engine has been shut down. We are no longer able to maintain level flight.Request descent to FL200.
二发已关车。我们不能保持平飞，请示下降到高度层 200.
The uncontained engine failure has caused parts of the fuselage to be damaged. Request emergency descent.
不含发动机的失效导致部分机身损坏，请示紧急下降。
Our left engine has ingested FOD. We are shutting down engines and holding position.
左发有外来物，我们正在关车并原地等待。
There is a huge gaping hole in the aisle, somehow the cabin floor has been punctured. We are re-seating passengers. Request holding.
过道出现很大的东，不知什么原因，客舱地板被穿透了。我们正在重新安排乘客座位，请示等待。
We have abnormal noise coming from the mid section of our fuselage, somewhere near the ceiling. Request descent and reduce speed.
机身中部靠近客舱顶部，有异常噪音。请示下降并减速。
We heard an explosion from the cabin. Request to stop climb.
客舱传来爆炸声，请示停止爬升。
We are unsure about the cause of the explosion. There are injuries in the cabin. We’ll give you an update as soon as possible.
我们不确定爆炸的原因。客舱有人受伤。我们一有消息将尽快给你们。
Some passengers have cuts and burn wounds due onboard explosion. Request diversion and medical services upon arrival.
由于机上爆炸，一些乘客有割伤和烧伤。请示备降和到场时医疗服务。
Ice is accumulating rapidly on the wings and fuselage. Request emergency descent to 6000 feet.
机翼和机身的积冰速度很快，请示紧急下降到 6000 英尺。
We are encountering moderate icing. Request immediate descent.
我们遇到了中度积冰，请示立即下降。
We made a diversion due to reports of freezing rain at our original destination.
我们备降是由于受到目的地机场冻雨报告。
We are on emergency descent due severe icing.
由于严重结冰，我们紧急下降了。
We are encountering clear ice. Request immediate right turn to heading 130.
我们遇到了明冰，请示立即右转至航向 130.
Rime ice was reported by previous aircraft during approach.
进近中前机报告有毛冰。
We cannot continue holding in icing conditions. Request descent immediately and cancel speed restrictions.
我们不能再结冰条件下继续等待。请示立即下降并取消速度限制。
We have a “Wind-shear Ahead” warning message. Request to delay takeoff or change to another runway.
我们出现了“前方风切变”警告信息，请示推迟起飞，或更换一条跑道。
We have a “Wind-shear Ahead” warning. Request to delay our approach.
我们出现了“前方风切变”警告，请示推迟进近。
We made the go around due to wind-shear warning.
我们复飞的原因是风切变警告。
We have received information of a new volcanic eruption. Will it affect our route?
我们收到火上喷发的一条新信息。会影响我们的航路吗？
We are unsure of our position due heavy fog. We are holding position.
由于浓雾，我们不确定当前位置，原地等待中。
We had a rapid airspeed decay due turbulence. Request immediate descent to FL390.
我们的空速由于颠簸而快速衰减，请示立即下降到高度层 390。
We had to descend immediately due to wind-shear at our cruise level. We didn’t have time to request descent as the frequency was busy.
我们由于巡航高度层风切变的原因而必须立即下降。由于刚才频率繁忙，我们没有时间请示下降。
The airplane began to buffet when climbing through FL380. We had to stop climb immediately to increase airspeed.
刚才上升通过高度层 380 时飞机开始抖振，我们必须立即停止爬升以增加空速。
We are flying near our maximum altitude. We cannot maintain airspeed in this turbulence.Request immediate descent.
我们正接近我们的最大高度飞行。我们不能在颠簸中保持空速，请示立即下降。
I apologize for the level bust, but we needed the altitude loss to recover from wind-shear.
很抱歉偏离指定高度，但我们需要损失高度来改出风切变。
We encountered heavy rain and had a temporary flame out on our right engine. Request immediate climb.
我们遇到了大雨，右发暂时熄火，请示立即上升。
We won’t have to deviate if you allow us to climb to FL430.
如允许我们上升到高度层 430，我们就不用偏置了。
The thunderstorms will last for about 40 minutes according to the weather update. Request diversion.
根据天气更新情况，雷暴将持续约 40 分钟。请示备降。
We have encountered severe clear air turbulence. Request immediate descent.
我们已遭受严重晴空颠簸，请示立即下降。
Request a general heading of 050 due to multiple cells ahead.
前方多个单体雷雨区，请示飞航向大约 050.
We have stopped on Runway 23 and will remain on the runway due heavy fog. I say again, we are still on the runway.
我们停在了 23 号跑道上，并且由于浓雾我们仍在跑道上。再说一遍，我们仍在跑道上。
There is heavy drifting fog. We think it is no longer safe to taxi. Request to hold at present position.
有较大平流雾，我们认为对滑行不安全，请示原地等待。
Frontal weather is quickly moving in from the west. If the holding is more than 10 minutes, we will have to divert.
锋面天气很快由西移动过来。如果等待超过 10 分钟，我们就必须要备降。
We made the go-around because strong convective currents on short final made our approach unstable.
我们复飞的原因是因为短五边很强的对流使进近不稳定。
There was temperature inversion when we descended through 3000 feet. Our airspeed dropped suddenly by 25 knots.
我们下降通过 3000 英尺时有逆温层。我们的空速突然掉了 25 节。
We performed the missed approach below the minimum because of advection fog. We could no longer see the runway lights.
由于平流雾，我们执行了低于最低高度的复飞。我们不能再看见跑道灯了。
The latest weather says that frontal weather and freezing rain is now stationary over the airport. Request diversion.
最新气象报说锋面天气和冻雨正在机场上空停留。请示备降。
We can’t find any gaps for at least 100 miles in the squall line covering our arrival route.Request diversion.
飑线覆盖了我们进场航路，至少 100 海里范围内我们都找不到任何空间穿越。请示备降。
We can see dust swirls approaching the airport and we’re concerned about low level wind-shear. Request holding.
我们能看到尘埃涡流接近机场，我们担心低空风切变。请示等待。
The latest SIGMET says a super-cell thunderstorm is developing at our destination. Is our flight affected?
最新重要气象报表明超级单体雷暴正在我们目的地机场形成。我们的航班受影响吗？
Request to continue our flight. Our ETA is in two hours and maybe the airport will have the runways cleared of snow by then.
请示继续飞行。我们的预达时刻是 2 小时后，可能机场会在那时将跑道上的雪除干净。
We had to make a quick heading change due ice pellets. You didn’t answer our request so we squawked 7700 and made the heading change.
我们因为冰丸必须快速改变航向。你没有回答我们的申请，因此我们设置应答机编码7700，并改变了航向。
We were struck by hail. Our airframe is severely damaged. Request emergency services.
我们被冰雹击中了。我们的机体严重受损。请示紧急服务。
We have just encountered a lightning strike. Some of our instruments have erroneous indications. Request diversion to the nearest suitable airport.
我们刚遭受雷击。一些仪表出现错误指示，请示备降到最近的合适机场。
We have had a lightning strike. So far no system seems to be affected. We will continue to our destination.
我们已遭遇雷击，目前为止没有系统受到影响，我们将继续前往目的地。
Roger heavy rain. Request to terminate our approach.
明白，大雨。请示终止进近。
Request to cancel our approach. The runway is not long enough and there are water patches.
请示取消进近。跑道长度不够，还有部分积水。
Request to cancel our approach. Braking action is poor and we’re concerned about hydroplaning during rollout.
请示取消进近。刹车效应差，我们担心滑跑时出现滑水现象。
Request holding instructions. We’ll attempt another approach when the rain showers become lighter.
请示等待指令。阵雨变小的时候，我们将重新进近。
We have received reports of freezing rain ranging from ground up to 5000 feet. Request diversion.
我们收到了冻雨报告，范围从地面到 5000 英尺。请示备降。
We have observed blowing sand in the vicinity of the airport. How long will this last?
我们已观察到在机场附近有吹沙。持续多长时间呢？
A sandstorm is forecast to reach the airport within 20 minutes. We won’t get airborne by then. Request cancel startup and tow back to the gate.
预计沙暴在 20 分钟内到达机场。我们到那时还不能升空，请示取消开车并拖回停机位。
Heavy blowing snow is expected to last for another 30 minutes. Request to terminate approach and holding instructions.
较大得到吹雪预计持续 30 分钟，请示终止进近、等待指令。
Runway is covered with patches of ice. Braking action is medium to poor.
跑道被大片结冰覆盖，刹车效应中等偏差。
Ice patches are covering the runway mostly along the runway edge. Uncontaminated runway width is about 30 meters.
成片结冰覆盖跑道边缘大部分地方。未污染跑道的宽度约 30 米。
A dissipating thunderstorm is ahead of us. We are near the zero-degree isotherm. Request deviate an additional 10 miles to the right.
消散雷暴在我们前方。我们接近零度等温线，请示再右偏 10 海里。
We have a visual on a tornado at our 10 o’clock, about 2 miles. Request immediate right turn.
我们在 10 点钟方向、大约 2 海里处目视龙卷风。请示立即右转。
The weather forecast says that the typhoon along our route will be intensifying. Request change our airway clearance.
天气预报说我们航路的台风将会增强，请示改变我们的航路许可。
The hurricane has gathered in strength and will affect all airports at the south coast. Request diversion.
飓风已大量聚集，而且将影响南海岸的全部机场。请示备降。
A Pilot overflying reported seeing virga above the runways. Request to terminate our approach.
一名飞越的飞行员报告在跑道上空看见了雨幡。请示终止进近。
Request immediate one eighty turn to the right due volcanic ash.
由于火山灰，请示立即 180 度右转。
We have entered volcanic ash. Our radios and engines are not working properly, now heading 235, and descending to FL 220, squawking 7700.
我们已经进入火山灰。无线电和发动机都不能正常工作，当前航向 235，下降到高度层 220 过程中，应答机编码 7700。
We are landing into the sun in heavy haze. Can you turn on the approach lights to maximum intensity?
我们在严重霾中迎太阳着陆。能把进近灯调到最大强度吗？
Lining up Runway 35. Runway lights are too bright. Request to dim the runway lights.
对正跑道 35 中。跑道灯太亮，请示调暗跑道灯。
There are red lights ahead of us. Confirm taxi instructions.
前方有红灯，证实滑行指令。
There is an obstruction ahead. Confirm taxi instructions.
前方有障碍物，证实滑行指令。
The NOTAM says this part of the taxiway is closed during this period, please verify.
航行通告说部分滑行道在这期间关闭，请核实。
The follow-me vehicle is leading us to taxiway L3. Our wings will not clear the otherairplanes on this narrow taxiway. We are stopping.
引导车正引导我们到滑行到 L3.在这条较窄的滑行道上我们的机翼无法避开其他飞机。我们停止滑行了。
We are stopping. The ground marshaller is still guiding us in, but I think my engine will hit the boarding bridge if we taxi any further.
我们停止了。地面引导员仍引导我们滑入，但我认为如果我们再滑入，我们的发动机将碰到廊桥。
We are stopping taxi. The boarding bridge is not at its designated position.
我们停止滑行了。廊桥不在指定位置。
We are shutting down our engines. There are boxes blown by the wind toward our aircraft.
我们正关车。风朝我们飞机方向吹来了一些盒子。
We had difficulty starting up our engines due strong tailwind. Request to change our pushback position facing west.
由于强顺风，我们启动发动机困难。请示改变推出位置，面朝西。
Another aircraft has collided with us. I’ll command an evacuation as soon as we both turn off our engines.
另一架飞机与我们相撞。在我们双方都关车后，我将下指令尽快撤离。
The tow bar has been bent. Our maintenance crew will inspect our nose wheel. Holding position.
拖杆弯了。我们的机务人员将检查前轮。原地等待。
The tug has swung around and collided with our forward fuselage. We are shutting down engines. Request stairs vehicle and shuttle bus.
拖车偏转撞到飞机前身。我们正关车。请示客梯车和摆渡车。
A catering truck collided with our aft fuselage. There are fumes in the cabin and we are quickly disembarking all passengers. Request fire services.
餐车撞到了我们的后机身。客舱有烟雾，我们正在尽快让所有乘客下机。请示消防服务。
The flaps were extended inadvertently and hit the fuel truck. We are disembarking all onboard personnel. Request fire services.
襟翼无意中被放出，碰到了油车。我们正在撤离机上所有人员。请示消防服务。
Our airplane nose has now lifted off the ground due to improper load and balance. Request ground maintenance.
由于不正确的配载平衡，飞机机头已经翘起，请示地面维护。
We have discovered leakage of dangerous goods in the cargo hold. Can you alert hazardous material specialists?
我们已发现货舱里的危险品泄露。你们能通知危险品专家吗？
Our cabin crew will direct all passengers to stay outside the runway after evacuation.
撤离后我们的客舱机组将指导所有乘客待在跑道外。
The outer main landing gear might have rolled over runway lights when we made the one eighty turn. Request personnel to inspect.
我们 180 度转弯时主起落架可能擦到了跑道灯。请示人员检查。
We have a suspicious bag on board. Request bomb squad.
机上有可疑的包，请示拆弹小组。
The passengers are evacuating. The bomb is still on board.
乘客正在撤离。炸弹还在飞机上。
A passenger has assembled a bomb in the lavatory. He is making threats. Request emergency services.
一名乘客已在厕所安装了一枚炸弹。他正在威胁我们，请示紧急服务。
Request a remote apron for parking our aircraft due bomb on board.
机上有炸弹，请示远机坪停机位。
We have had a tail strike. Request to stop climb at 3000 feet and return for landing.
我们已经机尾擦地，请示爬升至 3000 英尺返场着陆。
We have veered off the runway due asymmetric thrust. We are evacuating. Request emergency assistance.
由于不对称推力，我们在跑道上突然转向偏出了跑道，现在正在撤离。请示紧急救助。
We cannot get good climb profile due engine problems. Request maintain runway heading.
由于发动机问题，我们不能得到很好的爬升性能。请示保持跑道方向航向。
We made a very hard landing. We’ll need maintenance inspection before our next flight.Suggest you check the runway touchdown zone.
我们重着陆了，下次飞行前我们需要机务检查。建议你们检查跑道接地区。
The center of gravity is disturbed. We will relocate passengers prior to approach. Request holding.
重心位置有变，进近千我们需要重新安排乘客。请示等待。
Request a large airspace to maneuver due flight control problems.
由于飞行操纵问题，请示较大空域做机动。
My apologies for the deviation due the wrong altitude setting. Request further instructions.
抱歉由于高度表设置错误出现偏差，请示进一步指令。
My apologies for the level deviation. We were caught in a strong updraft.
抱歉高度偏离了，我们遇到了强上升气流。
We used too much speed brakes and penetrated our level. Did we cause any conflict?
我们使用了过量的减速板，穿过了我们的高度层。我们引起冲突了吗？
We were not informed of a frequency change. I will now monitor your frequency.
我们未得到频率改变的通知。我现在马上监听。
Unable visual approach due company policy. Request radar vectors.
公司政策原因不能目视进近。请示雷达引导。
Unable circling approach due company policy. Request diversion.
公司政策原因不能盘旋进近。请示备降。
Are we being vectored too close to the parallel aircraft?
我们引导得是否太靠近平行飞机了？
Is the preceding aircraft crossing our altitude?
前机正在穿越我们的高度吗？
I can read you, but I’m not sure you can hear me. I will squawk ident to comply with your instructions.
我能听到你，但我不确认你能听到我。我将应答机识别来遵守指令。
I see wildfire at my 10 o’clock, about 8 miles.
我在 10 点钟方向、大约 8 海里处看到了野火。
I have heard an aircraft in distress but no one’s responding. I can help relay his message.
我听到有飞机遇险了，但没人回应。我能帮助转报信息。
Message relay: The aircraft in distress will ditch in the ocean. His present coordinate is One Eight Degrees, One Five Minutes, North, One Six Zero Degrees, Five Two Minutes East.
转报：遇险飞机将海上迫降。目前坐标是 18 度 15 分北，160 度 52 分东。
The aircraft in distress says he will attempt to force land in an area about ten miles Northeast of his position.
遇险飞机说他将尝试在其位置东北 10 海里区域迫降。
Request offset 10 miles left to avoid the reported strong downdraft.
请示左偏 10 海里，避开已报告的强下降气流。
Request diversion. The latest weather at our destination suggests snow storm will last for 5hours.
请示备降。目的地机场最新天气表明雪暴将持续 5 小时。
Our radar shows a strong echo from the thunderstorm ahead. Request immediate right turn to avoid it.
雷达显示前方强雷暴回波。请示立即右转避开。
Request immediate one-eighty turn to the right due to possible hail ahead.
请示立即 180 度右转，避开前方冰雹。
We have three serious and five minor injuries on board. Request ambulances on arrival.
我们机上有三人重伤，五人轻伤。请示救护车到场。
One passenger is having difficulty breathing. Request descent to a lower level to reduce cabin altitude.
一名旅客呼吸困难，请示下降到较低高度以减小客舱高度。
A passenger activated the overhead emergency oxygen generator. Request airport security on arrival to detain this individual.
一名旅客触发了顶部紧急氧气发生器。请示机场保安到场拘留他。
A stressed passenger attempted to open an emergency exit. Request airport security on arrival.
一名闹情绪的旅客试图打开应急出口。请示机场保安到场。
We have a hostage situation. Request stair vehicles on standby to disembark the passengers.
我们有一个人质。请示客梯车待命以便让旅客下机。
We have a passenger with severe hyperventilation. He has received first aid but his condition is not improving. Request ambulance on arrival.
有一个旅客有严重的过度换气症。他得到了急救但情况没有好转。请示救护车到场。
We have a passenger with a suspected heart attack. Request diversion to a suitable airport.
有名旅客疑似有心脏病。请示备降到合适机场。
A pregnant passenger is in severe pain. Request priority landing and ambulance on arrival.
一名孕妇正承受剧痛。请示优先着陆和救护车到场。
There was a fight onboard among a few passengers. One of them is now bleeding seriously.Request police and ambulances on arrival.
几名旅客在机上打架。其中一个人现在流血严重。请求警察和救护车到场。
The purser told me the injured passenger has blood type O. Maybe this information is useful to the paramedics.
乘务长告诉我受伤旅客的血型是 O 型，或许该信息对急救医护人员有用。
We have an 8-month old infant with head injuries. Request ambulance on arrival.
我们有个 8 个月大的婴儿头部受伤。请示救护车到场。
A passenger is unconscious after suffering from seizure. The cabin crew is giving her first aid. We will advise if we require a diversion.
一名旅客癫痫发作后失去知觉。客舱机组正在急救。如需备降我们将告知你们。
Many passengers and crew were injured due severe turbulence. We will advise the number and severity of injuries when able.
由于严重颠簸，多名旅客和机组都受伤了。如能够，我们将告知受伤人数及受伤程度。
An elderly passenger has passed away. We will continue to our destination. Request ambulance on arrival.
一位年长的旅客去世了。我们将继续到目的地。请示救护车到场。
We found a passenger unconscious from a drug overdose in the lavatory. Request police and ambulance on arrival.
我们发现一名旅客在洗手间服药过量失去意识了。请示警察和救护车到场。
The sick passenger’s condition has improved. We no longer require the diversion. Request to continue to our destination.
生病旅客的情况已经好转。我们不再要求备降。请示继续飞往目的地。
We received an emergency call from the cabin, but now nobody is responding. We can hear shouting and disturbance. Our cabin crew might be under duress.
我们收到客舱紧急呼叫，但现在没人回应。我们能听见喊叫声和打斗声。客舱机组可能受到了胁迫。
We have a hijack situation on board. Can our destination airport provide armed intervention?
我们被劫机了。目的地机场能否提供武装干涉？
We can see two masked men with sharp weapons on our cockpit door surveillance camera.They are kicking the cockpit door.
我们通过驾驶舱监控摄像机看见两个头戴面具手拿利器的人。他们正在踢驾驶舱门。
I can see the area outside of the cockpit. There are two hijack suspects standing in the aisle.
我能看见驾驶舱外面区域。有两名劫机者正站在过道。
One of the terrorists is about forty-year old. He is about 180 cm tall, wearing a brown shirt and dark pants.
其中一名恐怖分子大约 40 岁，他有 180 厘米高，身穿棕色衬衫和深色裤子。
A terrorist is trying to access the cockpit. He is about 30 years old. He is wearing a hat and backpack.
一名恐怖分子正试图接近驾驶舱，他大约 30 岁，头戴一顶帽子，背有双肩包。
The purser reports there are over ten hijackers onboard. They are threatening to kill passengers if we don’t fly to another destination.
乘务长报告机上有超过 10 名劫机犯，他们正威胁我们如果不飞往另一个目的地，他们要杀死乘客。
Some of the hijackers are carrying sharp protruding weapons.
一些劫机犯拿着锋利、尖锐的武器。
There is a stand-off in the cabin. Some of the hijackers are carrying blades.
客舱已陷入僵持状态。一些劫机犯拿着刀片。
Terrorists started to injure passengers.
恐怖分子开始伤害旅客了。
We will remain on the runway. The hijackers have taken four hostages to the rear of the cabin.
我们将停留在跑道上。劫机犯已把四名人质带到了客舱后部。
Terrorists are threatening to start killing passengers and the crew.
恐怖分子威胁说他们要杀死旅客和机组了。
The air marshal and passengers have restrained five suspects. The situation is now under control.
安全员和乘客已经制服了 5 名疑犯。局面得到了控制。
A suspicious suitcase was found during the cabin inspection.
客舱检查中发现了可疑手提箱。
The air marshal is searching the aircraft interior for any suspicious articles.
安全员正在搜查飞机里的任何可疑物品。
Some explosives were discovered behind a panel near the back of the cabin.
客舱后部的一个面板后面发现一些爆炸物。
What do the bomb-disposal experts suggest we do?
拆弹专家建议我们做什么？
The cabin crew reports a passenger is behaving strangely.
客舱机组报告说一名旅客行为怪异。
A bomb has exploded and the cabin is full of smoke. Request emergency descent.
炸弹已爆炸，客舱到处是烟雾。请示紧急下降。
We are evacuating on the runway. Be advised the bomb is still on board.
我们正在跑道上紧急撤离。被告知炸弹仍在飞机上。
We are unsure of our position due to navigation failure. If any station can hear me, please respond.
由于导航失效，我们不确定位置。如果任何电台能听到我们，请回话。
We only have standby magnetic compass due instrument failure. Now heading 245. Request navigation assistance.
我们因仪表失效只有备用磁罗盘。现在航向 245，请示导航援助。
We are unsure of our position due FMS failure. Last known position five miles north of FUPAD, now heading 165 for weather avoidance.
由于飞行管理系统失效，我们不确定当前位置。最后已知位置是 PUPAD 以北 5 海里，当前航向 165 以避开天气。
We have navigation map drift. Request climb to MEA.
导航地图漂移，请示上升到最低航路高度。
Our cargo manifest shows that there are 80 kilograms of lithium batteries on board.
我们的货物舱单表明机上有 80 千克的锂电池。
A ramp inspection discovered crates of lithium batteries in the cargo hold. We are verifying. Request delay pushback.
机坪检查发现货舱有数箱锂电池，我们正在核实。请示延迟推出。
We had a smoke warning in the cargo hold. We have discharged the fire extinguisher. We are concerned about lithium batteries in that compartment.
我们的货舱有烟雾警告，已经释放灭火瓶。我们担心货舱的锂电池。
The cabin crew have used up all the portable extinguishers. Request diversion.
客舱机组已用完了手提灭火瓶。请示备降。
Request passenger stairs connect immediately after we stop on the runway. We want to disembark passengers as quickly as possible.
我们停止在跑道上后请示立即连接客梯车。我们想尽快让旅客离机。
We almost had a mid-air collision with another aircraft.
我们差一点与另一架飞机空中相撞。
The conflicting traffic is military. Request avoiding action.
冲突飞机是军用机，请示避让措施。
Does the flight path of the unknown aircraft converge with ours?
不明飞机的飞行路线和我们的会聚吗？
The conflicting traffic is gray, possibly a military aircraft.
冲突飞机是灰色的，可能是军用机。
We have traffic indication at 2 o’clock, 300 feet above our level.
冲突飞机显示在 2 点钟方位，高于我们 300 英尺。
We have a possible traffic conflict at 10 o’clock, converging with our flight path.
我们在 10 点钟方位可能有冲突飞机，该机与我们的飞行路线会聚。
We have a possible traffic conflict ahead. Request radar vectors for avoidance.
我们前方可能有冲突飞机，请示雷达引导避让。
Request right turn for traffic avoidance.
请示右转避让冲突飞机。
Unable to comply, TCAS RA.
不能照办，遵守 TCAS RA 通告
We nearly collided with that aircraft. We had very little vertical separation. Do you know the flight number of that aircraft?
我们几乎与那架飞机相撞，我们之间几乎没有垂直间隔。你们知道那架飞机的航班号吗？
Clear of conflict, request further instructions.
冲突解除，请示进一步指令。
We have injuries resulting from our TCAS maneuver. Request ambulance on arrival.
TCAS 机动导致部分旅客受伤。请示救护车到场。
Some of the cabin crew are injured. They were serving meals during the TCAS maneuver.
部分客舱机组受伤了。TCAS 机动时他们正在供餐。
Some passengers were injured because their seatbelts weren’t fastened.
一些旅客受伤是因为他们没有系安全带。
Some passengers have been scalded by hot drinks.
一些乘客被热饮烫伤了。
We have about thirty injured persons on board, four are very serious. Can you deliver this message to the medical staff that are standing by?
我们机上有三十人受伤，其中 4 让人受伤严重。你能把此消息告知待命的医务人员吗？
We overran the runway end. We are evacuating. Request emergency services.
我们冲出了跑道头，正在撤离。请示紧急服务。
We veered off the runway. We are evacuating near the runway and rapid exit J5.
我们偏出了跑道，正在撤离。我们的位置在跑道和快速脱离道口 J5 附近。
We will reach our minimum fuel if we are delayed any further.
如果进一步延误，我们将达到最低燃油量。
We are declaring minimum fuel. We will have less than 30 minutes endurance by the time we get to our destination.
我们宣布最低燃油量。，我们到达目的地机场后将有少于 30 分钟的续航时间。
We are declaring fuel emergency. Our endurance is 1 hour 58 minutes. We are 1 hour 30 minutes from the closest alternate airport.
我们宣布燃油紧急状况。我们的续航时间是 1 小时 58 分钟，而我们到最近备降场的时间是1 小时 30 分钟。
We are declaring fuel emergency. Request priority landing Runway 03R.
我们宣布燃油紧急状况。请示优先着陆，跑道 03 右。
We have been intercepted by a military aircraft. It is rocking its wings to indicate we should follow.
我们被一架军用机拦截了，它摇动机翼让我们跟着。
I’m trying to identify the type and nationality of the military aircraft. So far, no response on121.5.
我们正试着识别军用飞机的机型和国籍。到目前为止，121.5 频率仍没有回应。
The military aircraft is commanding us to land at the airfield below.
军用飞机正在命令我们在下面的机场着陆。
The military aircraft has made an abrupt maneuver indicating we may continue on this heading.
军用飞机已突然机动，表明我们可以继续保持此航向。
We are being escorted towards the national boundary by two military aircraft.
我们正在被两架军用飞机押送到国境线。
We are heading 085. This heading allows us to quickly exit the prohibited airspace.
我们当前航向 085.此航向可以让我们快速离开禁飞空域。
If we continue to make orbits we will exceed our duty time limit by the time we land.
如果继续转圈，我们将在落地时超出执勤期限制。
A crew member is incapacitated. Request diversion and medical assistance.
一名机组成员失能。请示备降和医疗救助。
They have revived the unconscious passenger by CPR procedure. It looks like he’ll be fine.Request to cancel the diversion.
他们通过心肺复苏程序使失去知觉的乘客恢复了意识。他好像转好，请示取消备降。
Confirm we are being vectored to fly overhead the airport for right downwind.
证实我们正雷达引导通过机场上空加入右三边。
Confirm we have enough separation from preceding aircraft.
证实我们与前机有足够间隔。
Unable to expedite climb due performance.
由于性能，不能快速爬升。
Negative contact due visibility.
由于能见度，不能看见（机场或飞机等）。
Unable, we are in IMC.
不能，我们在仪表天气条件。
Unable, we are only authorized during daytime VMC.
不能，我们只有白天目视气象条件的资格。
Unable noise abatement due company policy.
由于公司政策，不能执行减噪程序。
Did the previous controller tell you about our problem during radar handoff?
雷达移交时前一个管制员告诉你我们的问题了吗？
Is there a frequency change at this compulsory reporting point?
在此强制报告点需要切换频率吗？
Unable speed 180 knots. We need to maintain a good speed in clean configuration due icing.
不能保持速度 180 节。由于积冰，我们需要保持光洁构型下的指定速度。
Unable to reduce speed below mach decimal 74. You can vector us if you’d like.
速度不能低于马赫数 0.74（点 74）。如果可以，你可以雷达引导我们。
Request runway change for departure due high crosswind.
由于大侧风，请示更换跑道离场。
Request delay the approach due tail wind beyond limits.
由于顺风超限，请示推迟进近。
Request holding instructions due weather near the runway threshold.
由于跑道入口附近天气，请示等待指令。
Unable, an immediate right turn might not give us enough terrain clearance. Our turn radius is 4 miles at this speed.
不行。立即右转可能导致越障阈度不够。当前速度的转弯半径是 4 海里。
Sorry, there was a problem with my audio equipment. How do you read me now?
抱歉，我的音频设备有问题。现在你听我几个？
We had to overshoot because of wake turbulence.
我们必须复飞的原因是尾流。
Not ready for immediate takeoff due possible wake turbulence from departing heavy aircraft.
没有准备好立即起飞，刚起飞的重型机可能有尾流。
Unable CAT II approach due crew qualification.
不能 II 类盲降进近，机组没有资质。
Transmission blocked, say again.
干扰了，再说一遍。
Standby, high pilot workload.
稍等，飞行员工作负荷大。
Are you banning us from entry because of our airline or our aircraft type?
你禁止我们飞入是因为我们公司或我们的机型吗？
Our aircraft has the required certification and is approved by your Civil Aviation Authority for scheduled flight.
我们的飞机有相应资质，你们民航当局也批准执行定期航班。
We had to go around due to unstable approach.
因为不稳定进近，我们必须复飞。